<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sportify</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="eventdetail">eventdetail</string>
    <string name="eventrules">eventrules</string>
    <string name="eventcontact">eventcontact</string>



    <!-- //********************************  SOCIAL APP STRINGS **************************************************************/  -->


        <string name="label_create_post_activity">Create post</string>
        <string name="label_post_detail_activity">Post detail</string>
        <string name="label_image_detail_activity">Image</string>
        <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
        <string name="title_activity_create_profile">Create profile</string>
        <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
        <string name="title_activity_edit_profile">Edit profile</string>
        <string name="title_activity_edit_post">Edit post</string>

        <string name="text_take_photo">Take photo</string>
        <string name="text_pick_photo">Pick from Gallery</string>
        <string name="button_title_cancel">Cancel</string>
        <string name="button_ok">OK</string>

        <string name="hint_title">Title</string>
        <string name="hint_description">Description</string>

        <string name="message_post_was_created">Post was created</string>
        <string name="error_fail_create_post">Fail to create post</string>
        <string name="error_fail_load_image">Fail to load image</string>
        <string name="error_fail_crop_image">Fail to crop image</string>
        <string name="error_smaller_image">Image is too small. Required image size 100x100 px</string>
        <string name="error_incorrect_file_type">Incorrect file type</string>
        <string name="error_bigger_file">File size is bigger than 10Mb</string>
        <string name="message_creating_post">Creating post ..</string>
        <string name="message_saving">Saving ..</string>
        <string name="warning_empty_image">Image is required</string>
        <string name="warning_empty_title">Title is required</string>
        <string name="warning_empty_description">Description is required</string>
        <string name="error_post_title_length">Max length of the title should be less than 255 symbols</string>
        <string name="error_fail_remove_post">Fail to remove post</string>
        <string name="message_post_was_removed">Post was removed</string>
        <string name="error_fail_update_post">Fail to update post</string>
        <string name="error_post_was_removed">Post was removed</string>
        <string name="confirm_deletion_post">Delete this post?</string>

        <string name="comment_text_hint">Enter your comment…</string>
        <string name="button_post_comment">Post comment</string>

        <string name="label_comments">Comments (%1$d):</string>

        <string name="create_post_menu_label">Post</string>
        <string name="create_post_full_menu_label">Create post</string>
        <string name="sign_out_menu_label">Sign out</string>
        <string name="edit_profile_menu_label">Edit profile</string>
        <string name="button_title_save">Done</string>
        <string name="button_title_continue">Continue</string>

        <!-- Strings related to registration and login -->
        <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
        <string name="prompt_name">Name</string>
        <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
        <string name="prompt_conf_password">Confirm password</string>
        <string name="action_create_profile">Continue</string>
        <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
        <string name="error_profile_name_length">Max length of the name should be less than 120 symbols</string>
        <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
        <string name="error_confirm_password">Wrong password confirmation</string>
        <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
        <string name="permissions_not_granted">Cancelling, required permissions are not granted</string>
        <string name="error_fail_create_profile">Fail to create profile</string>
        <string name="error_fail_update_profile">Fail to update profile</string>
        <string name="text_login">Thank you for using our application! Please, sign in for continue your action.</string>
        <string name="error_authentication">Authentication failed.</string>
        <string name="error_google_play_services">Google Play Services error.</string>
        <string name="button_login_with_facebook">Login with facebook</string>
        <string name="button_login_with_google">Login with google</string>


        <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
        <string name="removing">Removing...</string>
        <string name="error_general">Somthing went wrong.</string>
        <string name="error_general_post">Somthing went wrong with post, id: %1$s</string>
        <string name="internet_connection_failed">No internet connection</string>

        <!-- Strings related to login -->

        <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
        <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
        <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

        <string name="profile_menu_item">Profile</string>
        <string name="collapse_text_label">show less</string>
        <string name="expand_text_label">show more</string>
        <string name="add_complain">Complain</string>
        <string name="edit_post_menu">Edit post</string>
        <string name="delete_post_menu">Delete post</string>
        <string name="complain_text">You can complain to this post if it contains violence,
        bullying and threats, hate speech, tragic events and sexually explicit contents.
        Nobody will see the post if you complain to it. You can\'t delete your complain.</string>

        <string name="send_comment_button_label">Send</string>
        <string name="posted_by_label">Posted by:</string>

        <plurals name="posts_counter_format">
            <item quantity="one">post</item>
            <item quantity="other">posts</item>
        </plurals>

        <plurals name="likes_counter_format">
            <item quantity="one">like</item>
            <item quantity="other">likes</item>
        </plurals>

        <string name="posts_label">Posts:</string>
        <string name="complain_sent">Complain was sent successfully</string>
        <string name="now_time_range">now</string>

        <string name="duration_minutes_shortest">%1$d m</string>
        <string name="duration_hours_shortest">%1$d h</string>
        <string name="duration_days_shortest">%1$d d</string>
        <string name="duration_week_shortest">%1$d w</string>

        <string name="post_image_transition_name" translatable="false">post_image_transition</string>
        <string name="post_author_image_transition_name" translatable="false">post_author_image_transition_name</string>
        <string name="message_new_post_was_created">New post was created</string>

        <plurals name="new_posts_counter_format">
            <item quantity="one">%1$d new post</item>
            <item quantity="other">%1$d new posts</item>
        </plurals>

        <string name="edit_comment_menu_item">Edit</string>
        <string name="delete_comment_menu_item">Delete</string>
        <string name="message_comment_was_removed">Comment was removed</string>
        <string name="message_comment_was_edited">Comment was edited</string>
        <string name="title_edit_comment">Edit comment</string>

        <!--Firebase errors-->
        <string name="permission_denied_error">Please check your rules to access the Firebase Realtime Database</string>
    <string name="very_severely_underweight">Very Severely Underweight</string>
    <string name="severely_underweight">Severely Underweight</string>
    <string name="underweight">Underweight</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="overweight">Overweight</string>
    <string name="Moderate_Obese">Moderate Obese</string>
    <string name="Severely_Obese">Severely Obese</string>
    <string name="Very_Severely_Obese">Very Severely Obese</string>



    <!-- //********************************  WATER INTAKE TRACKER **************************************************************/  -->

    <!-- settings-->
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="activity_settings_title">Settings</string>


    <!-- fragments preferences title & summary  water calculation-->
    <string name="pref_training_title">Training</string>
    <string name="pref_weight_title">Weight (kg)</string>
    <string name="pref_water_need_title">Daily Need</string>
    <string name="pref_gender_title">Gender</string>

    <string name="pref_notif_enable_title">Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_notif_sound_title">Sounds</string>
    <string name="pref_notif_interval_time_title">Time interval</string>
    <string name="pref_sounds_title">Sounds</string>


    <string name="wake_up_review">2 glasses of water after waking up - helps activate internal organs</string>
    <string name="sleep_review">1 glass of water before going to bed - avoids stroke or heart attack</string>
    <string name="shower_review">1 glass of water before taking a shower - helps lower blood pressure </string>
    <string name="meal_review">1 glass of water 30 before a meal - helps digestion</string>
    <string name="lose_weight">Water speeds up the metabolism. To lose extra weight - drink more water</string>
    <string name="lack_water">The brain and blood vessels function poorly with a lack of water. To prevent this from happening, maintain a normal water balance</string>
    <string name="title_activity_history_chart">historyChartActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>


    <!-- //********************************end -  WATER INTAKE TRACKER **************************************************************/  -->


    <!-- //********************************  PLAYER INFO **************************************************************/  -->

    <string name="p1_info">
Cristiano Ronaldo is a Portuguese professional footballer who plays as a forward for Spanish club Real Madrid and the Portugal national team. Often considered the best player in the world and widely regarded as one of the greatest of all time,[note 1] Ronaldo has five Ballon d Or awards, the most for a European player and is tied for most all-time. He is the first player in history to win four European Golden Shoes. He has won 25 trophies in his career, including five league titles, four UEFA Champions League titles and one UEFA European Championship. A prolific goalscorer, Ronaldo holds the records for most official goals scored in the top five European leagues (391), the UEFA Champions League (117), the UEFA European Championship (29) and the FIFA Club World Cup (7), as well as most goals scored in a UEFA Champions League season (17). He has scored more than 600 senior career goals for club and country.
</string>

    <string name="p2_info">
        LeBron Raymone James Sr.is an American professional basketball player for the Cleveland Cavaliers of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Widely regarded as one of the greatest NBA players of all time, he has won three NBA championships, four NBA Most Valuable Player Awards, three NBA Finals MVP Awards, three NBA All-Star Game MVP Awards, two Olympic gold medals, an NBA scoring title, and the NBA Rookie of the Year Award. James is a 14-time NBA All-Star, 11-time All-NBA first teamer, and five-time All-Defensive first teamer. He is also the Cavaliers all-time scoring leader, the NBA All-Star Game career scoring leader, and the NBA career playoff scoring leader.
James played high school basketball at St. Vincent–St. Mary High School in his hometown of Akron, Ohio, where he was highly promoted in the national media as a future NBA superstar. After graduating, he was selected by his home team, the Cleveland Cavaliers, as the first overall pick of the 2003 NBA draft. James led Cleveland to the franchises first Finals appearance in 2007, ultimately losing to the San Antonio Spurs. In 2010, he left the Cavaliers for the Miami Heat, a controversial move featured in an ESPN special titled The Decision. James spent four seasons with the Heat, reaching the Finals all four years and winning back-to-back championships in 2012 and 2013. In 2013, he led Miami on a 27-game winning streak, the third longest in league history. Following his final season with the Heat in 2014, James opted out of his contract and returned to the Cavaliers. From 2015 to 2017, he led the Cavaliers to three consecutive Finals, winning his third championship in 2016 to end Clevelands 52-year professional sports title drought.
</string>

    <string name="p3_info">
Lionel Andrés Messi Cuccittini is an Argentine professional footballer who plays as a forward for Spanish club Barcelona and the Argentina national team. Often considered the best player in the world and regarded by many as the greatest of all time, Messi has a record-tying five Ballon dOr awards,[note 2] four of which he won consecutively, and a record-tying four European Golden Shoes.[note 3] He has spent his entire professional career with Barcelona, where he has won 30 trophies, including eight La Liga titles, four UEFA Champions League titles, and five Copas del Rey. Both a prolific goalscorer and a creative playmaker, Messi holds the records for most official goals scored in La Liga (374), a La Liga season (50), a club football season in Europe (73), a calendar year (91), El Clásico (25), as well as those for most assists made in La Liga (149) and the Copa América (11). He has scored over 600 senior career goals for club and country.
</string>

    <string name="p4_info">
Roger Federer is a Swiss professional tennis player who is currently ranked world No. 1 in mens singles tennis by the Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP).[2] Federer has won 20 Grand Slam singles titles—the most in history for a male player—and has held the world No. 1 spot in the ATP rankings for a record total of 307 weeks, including 237 consecutive weeks. After turning professional in 1998, he was continuously ranked in the top ten from October 2002 to November 2016. He re-entered the top ten following his victory at the 2017 Australian Open.
</string>

    <string name="p5_info">
Philip Alfred Mickelson is an American professional golfer. He has won 43 events on the PGA Tour, including five major championships: three Masters titles (2004, 2006, 2010), a PGA Championship (2005),[1] and an Open Championship (2013).Mickelson is one of 16 players in the history of golf to win at least three of the four majors.[3] He has won every major except the U.S. Open, where he has finished runner-up a record six times.
</string>


    <string name="p6_info">
Neymar da Silva Santos Júnior commonly known as Neymar or Neymar Jr., is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a forward for French club Paris Saint-Germain and the Brazil national team.
Neymar came into prominence at an early age at Santos, where he made his professional debut aged 17. He helped the club win two successive Campeonato Paulista championships, a Copa do Brasil, and the 2011 Copa Libertadores, Santos first continental title since 1963. Neymar was twice named the South American Footballer of the Year, in 2011 and 2012, before relocating to Europe to join Barcelona. As part of Barças attacking trio with Lionel Messi and Luis Suárez, he won the continental treble of La Liga, the Copa del Rey, and the UEFA Champions League in the 2014–15 season, followed the next year by the domestic double. He came third for the FIFA Ballon dOr in 2015. In August 2017, Neymar moved from Barcelona to Paris Saint-Germain in a transaction worth €222 million, making him the worlds most expensive player
</string>

    <string name="p7_info">
Usain St Leo Bolt is a retired Jamaican sprinter. He is the first person to hold both the 100 metres and 200 metres world records since fully automatic time became mandatory. He also holds the world record as a part of the 4 × 100 metres relay. He is the reigning Olympic champion in these three events. Due to his dominance and achievements in sprint competition, he is widely considered to be the greatest sprinter of all time.An eight-time Olympic gold medalist, Bolt won the 100 m, 200 m and 4 × 100 m relay at three consecutive Olympic Games, although he subsequently forfeited one of the gold medals (as well as the world record set therein) nine years after the fact due to a teammates disqualification for doping offences. He gained worldwide popularity for his double sprint victory at the 2008 Beijing Olympics in world record times. Bolt is the only sprinter to win Olympic 100 m and 200 m titles at three consecutive Olympics (2008, 2012 and 2016); this is a feat referred to as the "triple double" that will be very difficult for anyone to duplicate.
</string>

    <string name="p8_info">
Kevin Wayne Durant is an American professional basketball player for the Golden State Warriors of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He has won an NBA championship, an NBA Most Valuable Player Award, the Bill Russell NBA Finals Most Valuable Player Award, the NBA All-Star Game Most Valuable Player Award, four NBA scoring titles, the NBA Rookie of the Year Award, and two Olympic gold medals. Durant has also been selected to seven All-NBA teams and nine NBA All-Star teams.Durant was a heavily recruited high school prospect who was widely regarded as the second-best player in his class. He played one season of college basketball for the University of Texas, where he won numerous year-end awards and became the first freshman to be named Naismith College Player of the Year. In 2007, he was selected as the second overall pick by the Seattle SuperSonics in the NBA draft. After his rookie season, the team relocated to Oklahoma City and became the Thunder. Behind Durants leadership and his pairing with All-Star guard Russell Westbrook, the Thunder emerged as a perennial title contender, advancing as far as the NBA Finals in 2012, where they lost to the Miami Heat. He played nine seasons in Oklahoma City before signing with Golden State in 2016, winning a championship in his debut season.
</string>

    <string name="p9_info">
Rafael "Rafa" Nadal Parera is a Spanish professional tennis player, currently ranked world No. 2 in mens singles tennis by the Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP).[6] Known as "The King of Clay",[a] he is widely regarded as the greatest clay-court player in history.[b] Nadals evolution into an all-court threat has established him as one of the greatest tennis players of all time.Nadal has won 16 Grand Slam singles titles, 30 ATP World Tour Masters 1000 titles, 19 ATP World Tour 500 tournaments, and the 2008 Olympic gold medal in singles. In majors, Nadal has won 10 French Open titles, three US Open titles, two Wimbledon titles, and one Australian Open title. He was also a member of the winning Spain Davis Cup team in 2004, 2008, 2009, and 2011. In 2010, he became the seventh male player in history and youngest of five in the Open Era to achieve the Career Grand Slam at age 24. He is the second male player, after Andre Agassi, to complete the singles Career Golden Slam. In 2011, Nadal was named the Laureus World Sportsman of the Year.
</string>

    <string name="p10_info">
Eldrick Tont "Tiger" Woods is an American professional golfer who is among the most successful golfers of all time. He has been one of the highest-paid athletes in the world for several years.
Following an outstanding junior, college, and amateur career, Woods was 20 years old when he turned professional at the end of summer in 1996. By the end of April 1997, he had won three PGA Tour events in addition to his first major, the 1997 Masters. Woods won this tournament by 12 strokes in a record-breaking performance and earned $486,000. He first reached the number one position in the world rankings in June 1997, less than a year after turning pro. Throughout the 2000s, Woods was the dominant force in golf—he won the 2000 U.S. Open by an incredible 15-shot margin. He was the top-ranked golfer in the world from August 1999 to September 2004 (264 weeks) and again from June 2005 to October 2010 (281 weeks).
</string>


    <string name="p11_info">
Wardell Stephen Curry II (/st?f?n/ STEF-?n; born March 14, 1988) is an American professional basketball player for the Golden State Warriors of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Many players and analysts have called him the greatest shooter in NBA history.[1] In 2014–15, Curry won the NBA Most Valuable Player Award and led the Warriors to their first championship since 1975. The following season, he became the first player in NBA history to be elected MVP by a unanimous vote and to lead the league in scoring while shooting above 50–40–90. That same year, the Warriors broke the record for the most wins in an NBA season en route to reaching the 2016 NBA Finals, which they lost to the Cleveland Cavaliers. Curry helped the Warriors return to the NBA Finals for a third straight year in 2017, where he won his second NBA championship.
    </string>

    <string name="p12_info">
Novak Djokovic (Serbian: Novak Ðokovic, born 22 May 1987) is a Serbian professional tennis player who is currently ranked world No. 12 in mens singles tennis by the Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP).Djokovic has won 12 Grand Slam singles titles, five ATP Finals titles, 30 Masters 1000 series titles, 12 ATP World Tour 500 tournaments, and has held the No. 1 spot in the ATP rankings for a total of 223 weeks. In majors, Djokovic has won six Australian Open titles, three Wimbledon titles, two US Open titles and one French Open title. In 2016, he became the eighth player in history to achieve the Career Grand Slam. Following his victory at the 2016 French Open, he became the third man to hold all four major titles at once, the first since Rod Laver in 1969,[6] and the first ever to do so on three different surfaces.[7] Given these achievements, Djokovic is considered one of the greatest tennis players of all time.

</string>

<string name="p13_info">
Virat Kohli (About this sound pronunciation (help·info); born 5 November 1988) is an Indian international cricketer who currently captains the India national team. A right-handed batsman, often regarded as one of the best batsmen in the world,[4] Kohli is ranked as one of the worlds most famous athletes by ESPN[5] and one of the most valuable athlete brands by Forbes[6]. He plays for the Royal Challengers Bangalore in the Indian Premier League (IPL), and has been the teams captain since 2013.
</string>

<string name="p14_info">

</string>

<string name="p15_info">
MS Dhoni; born 7 July 1981) is an Indian international cricketer who captained the Indian national team in limited-overs formats from 2007 to 2016 and in Test cricket from 2008 to 2014. An attacking right-handed middle-order batsman and wicket-keeper, he is widely regarded as one of the greatest finishers in limited-overs cricket.[2][3][4][5] He is also regarded as one of the best wicket-keepers in world cricket and is known to have very fast hands.[6][7] He made his One Day International (ODI) debut in December 2004 against Bangladesh, and played his first Test a year later against Sri Lanka.Dhoni has been the recipient of many awards, including the ICC ODI Player of the Year award in 2008 and 2009 (the first player to win the award twice), the Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna award in 2007, the Padma Shri, Indias fourth highest civilian honour, in 2009 and the Padma Bhushan, Indias third highest civilian honour, in 2018.[8] He was named as the captain of the ICC World Test XI in 2009, 2010 and 2013. He has also been selected a record 8 times in ICC World ODI XI teams, 5 times as captain. The Indian Territorial Army conferred the honorary rank of Lieutenant Colonel[9] to Dhoni on 1 November 2011. He is the second Indian cricketer after Kapil Dev to receive this honour.

</string>

    <string name="p16_info">
Ronda Jean Rousey ( born February 1, 1987) is an American professional wrestler, actress, and former mixed martial artist and judoka. She is currently signed to WWE, performing on the Raw brand.Rousey was the first American woman to earn an Olympic medal in judo (bronze), which she won at the 2008 Summer Olympics in Beijing. She is the former UFC Womens Bantamweight Champion, as well as the last Strikeforce Womens Bantamweight Champion. She won 12 consecutive MMA fights, six in the Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC), before suffering her first loss, to Holly Holm in November 2015. She won 11 of those fights in the first round, nine of them by armbar submission. Rousey trains under Gokor Chivichyan of the Hayastan MMA Academy, and Edmond Tarverdyan of the Glendale Fighting Club.
</string>


    <string name="p17_info">
Jordan Alexander Spieth ( born July 27, 1993) is an American professional golfer on the PGA Tour and former world number one in the Official World Golf Ranking. He is a three-time major winner and the 2015 FedEx Cup champion.[1] In April 2016, Time magazine named Spieth to its list of the "100 Most Influential People", noting that he "exemplifies everything thats great about sports."Spieths first major win came in the 2015 Masters Tournament, when he shot a 270 (-18) and pocketed $1.8 million. He tied the 72-hole record set by Tiger Woods in 1997 and became the second youngest golfer (behind Woods) to win the Masters.
</string>

    <string name="p18_info">
Kaká made his professional club debut at age 18 at São Paulo FC in Brazil in 2001. After being named to the Bola de Ouro as the best player in the 2002 Campeonato Brasileiro, in 2003 he joined Italian club A.C. Milan for a fee of €8.5 million. At Milan, the club where he spent his prime years, Kaká won a Serie A title and was named the Serie A Footballer of the Year twice. In 2005, Milan finished runners up in the 2005 UEFA Champions League Final to Liverpool F.C., with Kaká, the top assist provider of the tournament, named the UEFA Club Midfielder of the Year. Two years later he led Milan to win the 2007 UEFA Champions League Final and was the tournaments top goal scorer. Kakás pace, creative passing, goal scoring and dribbles from midfield saw him win the FIFA World Player of the Year, the Ballon dOr, the UEFA Club Footballer of the Year and the IFFHS Worlds Best Playmaker awards.
</string>

    <string name="p19_info">
Serena Jameka Williams (born September 26, 1981)[1] is an American professional tennis player. The Womens Tennis Association (WTA) has ranked her world No. 1 in singles on eight separate occasions over the last 15 years from 2002 to 2017. She became the world No. 1 for the first time on July 8, 2002. On her sixth occasion, she held the ranking for 186 consecutive weeks, tying the record set by Steffi Graf for the most consecutive weeks as world No. 1 by a female tennis player. In total, she has been world No. 1 for 319 weeks, which ranks third in the Open Era among female players behind Graf and Martina Navratilova. Some commentators, players and sports writers regard her as the greatest female tennis player of all time.[a][17][18] On April 19, 2017, she announced a hiatus from tennis until 2018 because of pregnancy.

</string>

    <string name="p20_info">
Kei Nishikori ( born 29 December 1989) is a Japanese professional tennis player. He is the only male Japanese tennis player ever to be ranked inside the top 5 in singles, and first reached his career-high singles ranking of world No. 4 in March 2015. He is currently ranked world No. 25 by the Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP) as of March 5, 2018.He has won 11 singles titles and was runner-up at the 2014 US Open,[4] making him the first male player representing an Asian country to reach a Grand Slam singles final.[5] He also reached the semifinals at the US Open in 2016. He also became the first man from Asia to qualify for the ATP World Tour Finals and reached the semifinals in 2014 and 2016.
</string>

    <string name="p21_info">
Thomas Edward Patrick Brady Jr. (born August 3, 1977) is an American football quarterback for the New England Patriots of the National Football League (NFL). He is one of only two players to win five Super Bowls (the other being defensive player Charles Haley) and the only player to win them all playing for one team.After playing college football for the University of Michigan, Brady was drafted by the Patriots in the sixth round of the 2000 NFL Draft. Due to his late draft selection, Brady is considered to be the biggest "steal" in the history of the NFL Draft.[1][2][3] In Bradys 16 seasons as a starter,[a] he has quarterbacked the Patriots to eight Super Bowl appearances, the most for any player in history.
</string>


    <string name="p22_info">
He began his professional career at Southampton, playing at left-back and earning acclaim as a free kick specialist. Bale moved to Tottenham Hotspur in 2007, for an eventual £7 million fee. During his time at Tottenham, managerial and tactical shifts saw him transform into a more attacking player. From the 2009–10 season, under the guidance of Harry Redknapp, Bale became an integral part of the team, rising to international attention during the 2010–11 UEFA Champions League. In 2011 and 2013 he was named PFA Players Player of the Year, and was named in the UEFA Team of the Year. In 2013, he was also named PFA Young Player of the Year, the FWA Footballer of the Year and the Premier League Player of the Season. He was nominated to the PFA Team of the Year three times in a row between 2011 and 2013.

    </string>

    <string name="p23_info">
Maria Sharapova is a Russian professional tennis player. A United States resident since 1994,[3] Sharapova has competed on the WTA tour since 2001. She has been ranked world No. 1 in singles by the WTA on five separate occasions, for a total of 21 weeks. She is one of ten women, and the only Russian, to hold the career Grand Slam. She is also an Olympic medalist, having earned silver for Russia in womens singles at the 2012 Summer Olympics in London.
Sharapova became the world No. 1 for the first time on August 22, 2005, at the age of 18, and last held the ranking for the fifth time for four weeks from June 11, 2012, to July 8, 2012.[4][5] Her 35 singles titles and five Grand Slam titles—two at the French Open and one each at the Australian Open, Wimbledon, and US Open—rank third among active players, behind Serena and Venus Williams. She won the year-ending WTA Finals in her debut in 2004. She has also won three doubles titles.

</string>

    <string name="p24_info">
Dwyane Wade is an American professional basketball player for the Miami Heat of the National Basketball Association (NBA). After a successful college career at Marquette, Wade was drafted fifth overall in the 2003 NBA draft by Miami. In his third season, Wade led the Heat to their first NBA Championship in franchise history and was named the 2006 NBA Finals MVP. At the 2008 Summer Olympics, Wade led the United States mens basketball team, commonly known as the "Redeem Team", in scoring, and helped them capture the gold medal. In the 2008–09 season, Wade led the league in scoring and earned his first NBA scoring title. With LeBron James and Chris Bosh, Wade helped guide Miami to four consecutive NBA Finals from 2011 to 2014, winning back-to-back championships in 2012 and 2013. After 1½ seasons away from the Heat with the Chicago Bulls and Cleveland Cavaliers, Wade was traded back to Miami in February 2018. A 12-time NBA All-Star, Wade is Miamis all-time leader in points, games, assists and steals, shots made and shots taken.

</string>

    <string name="p25_info">
McGregor is the Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) lightweight champion and former featherweight champion. McGregor has also competed as a welterweight in mixed martial arts (MMA), and light middleweight in boxing. McGregor is 2nd on the UFCs pound for pound rankings.McGregor is the only fighter to be champion in two UFC divisions simultaneously: he defeated long time featherweight champion José Aldo at UFC 194 in 13 seconds, which is the fastest UFC title fight victory, and won the UFC lightweight belt against Eddie Alvarez at UFC 205.McGregor began his professional boxing career in 2017. In his debut boxing match, he was defeated by Floyd Mayweather Jr. via technical knockout.McGregor is the biggest pay-per-view (PPV) draw in MMA history, having headlined four out of the six highest-selling UFC pay-per-view events.[13] His headline bout with Nate Diaz at UFC 202 drew 1.65 million PPV buys, the most ever for an MMA event.[14] His boxing match with Mayweather drew 4.3 million PPV buys in North America, the second most in history.
</string>

    <string name="p26_info">
Zlatan Ibrahimovic ( born 3 October 1981) is a Swedish professional footballer who plays as a forward for Manchester United. He was also a member of the Sweden national team from 2001 to 2016, serving as captain from 2010 until his retirement.[4] Primarily a striker, he is a prolific goalscorer, who is best known for his technique, creativity, strength, ability in the air, and his powerful and accurate striking ability. He is currently the second-most decorated active footballer in the world, having won 32 trophies in his career.
</string>


    <string name="p27_info">
James David Rodríguez Rubio commonly known simply as James, is a Colombian professional footballer who plays as an attacking midfielder or winger for German club Bayern Munich on loan from Real Madrid, and captains the Colombia national team. He is commonly ranked as one of the best players of his generation.[1][2][3] He is praised for his technique, vision and playmaking skills, and often referred as the successor to his compatriot Carlos Valderrama.James became well known in Europe during his time at Porto, winning several trophies and individual awards during his three years at the club. In 2014, James moved from AS Monaco to Real Madrid for a transfer fee of £63 million
</string>

    <string name="p28_info">
James Harden is an American professional basketball player for the Houston Rockets of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Harden played college basketball for Arizona State, where he was named a consensus All-American and Pac-10 Player of the Year in 2009. Harden was selected with the third overall pick in the 2009 NBA draft by the Oklahoma City Thunder.[1] In 2012, he was named NBA Sixth Man of the Year with the Thunder and helped the team reach the NBA Finals.
</string>

    <string name="p29_info">
Sánchez began his career as a youth player for Cobreloa at age 17, completing a season at the club before relocating to Italy to play for Udinese in 2006. He won his first trophies in the following seasons, winning consecutive league titles in loans spells to Colo-Colo and River Plate. In 2008, he returned to Udinese, becoming an integral member of the team in his first full season at the club. After three fruitful seasons in Italy, Sánchez moved to Barcelona in a transfer worth €30 million (£25 million), becoming the most expensive Chilean player of all time.

</string>

    <string name="p30_info">
Özil plays mostly as an attacking midfielder, but can also be deployed as a winger. He began his senior career as a member of his hometown club Schalke 04 in the Bundesliga, departing two seasons later to join Werder Bremen for €5 million. He garnered break-out attention at the 2010 FIFA World Cup, where at age 22, Özil was instrumental in the sides campaign where they reached the semi-finals, losing to eventual champions Spain. He was also nominated for the Golden Ball Award, as well as being ranked first in assists in major European and domestic competitions with 25.[4] This garnered him a €15 million transfer to La Liga club Real Madrid.

</string>

    <string name="p31_info">
Wayne Rooney is an English professional footballer who plays for Premier League club Everton. He has played much of his career as a forward, and he has also been used in various midfield roles. He is the record goalscorer for the England national team and for Manchester United. At club level, he has won every honour available in English, European and Continental football, with the exception of the European Super Cup.[3] Along with Michael Carrick, he is the only English player to win the Premier League, FA Cup, UEFA Champions League, League Cup, UEFA Europa League and FIFA Club World Cup.

</string>


    <string name="p32_info">
Sir Andrew Barron Murray, OBE (born 15 May 1987) is a British professional tennis player from Scotland currently ranked world no. 29 in mens singles as of March 5, 2018.[6] Murray represents Great Britain in his sporting activities and is a three-time Grand Slam tournament winner, two-time Olympic champion, Davis Cup champion and the winner of the 2016 ATP World Tour Finals.Murray defeated Novak Djokovic in the 2012 US Open final, becoming the first British player since 1977, and the first British man since 1936, to win a Grand Slam singles tournament. Murray is also the first British man to win more than one Wimbledon singles title since Fred Perry in 1935.

    </string>

    <string name="p33_info">
Derrick Rose is an American professional basketball player for the Minnesota Timberwolves of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He played one year of college basketball for the Memphis Tigers before being drafted first overall by his hometown Chicago Bulls in the 2008 NBA draft.[1] After being named the NBA Rookie of the Year, Rose, at age 22, became the youngest player to win the NBA Most Valuable Player Award in 2011.Rose was born and raised in the Chicago area, and attended Simeon Career Academy. He was highly recruited by NCAA scouts and coaches, eventually choosing to join the University of Memphis under Coach John Calipari. Rose led the Memphis Tigers to the most wins in NCAA history (a 38-2 record), their first number one ranking in 25 years, and an appearance in the NCAA Championship game. In 2009, an NCAA investigation revealed that Roses SAT scores had been invalidated, and as a result, the NCAA vacated Memphis entire 2007–08 season.
</string>

    <string name="p34_info">
Kyrie Irving is an American professional basketball player for the Boston Celtics of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He was named NBA Rookie of the Year after being selected by the Cleveland Cavaliers with the first overall pick in the 2011 NBA draft. A five-time NBA All-Star, Irving was selected to the All-NBA Third Team in 2015. He won an NBA championship with the Cavaliers in 2016.Irving played college basketball for the Duke Blue Devils before joining the Cavaliers. He was named the NBA All-Star Game Most Valuable Player (MVP) in 2014. In the 2016 NBA Finals, he made a three-point field goal with 53 seconds remaining in a tied Game 7 to help lead the Cavaliers to a championship over the Golden State Warriors. After losing in the Finals in a rematch against the Warriors in 2017, Irving requested a trade, and he was dealt to Boston. Irving has also played for the United States national team, with whom he has won gold at the 2014 FIBA Basketball World Cup and the 2016 Summer Olympics.

</string>

    <string name="p35_info">
Russell Westbrook is an American professional basketball player for the Oklahoma City Thunder of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He is a seven-time NBA All-Star, and a two-time NBA All-Star Game Most Valuable Player, winning consecutive awards in 2015 and 2016. He is also an six-time All-NBA Team member and led the league in scoring in 2014–15 and 2016–17. In 2017, Westbrook became one of two players in NBA history to average a triple-double for a season, along with Oscar Robertson in 1962. He also set a record for the most triple-doubles in a season, with 42.[2] He was subsequently named the 2016–17 NBA Most Valuable Player.

</string>

    <string name="p36_info">
Antoine Griezmann is a French professional footballer who plays as a forward for Spanish club Atlético Madrid and the French national team.He began his career at Real Sociedad, making his debut in 2009 and winning the Segunda División title in his first season. Across five seasons there, he scored 52 goals in 201 official matches. In 2014, he transferred to Atlético Madrid for €30 million. For his performances throughout 2016, he was shortlisted for the Ballon dOr 2016 Award in which he finished in third place.
</string>


    <string name="p37_info">
Andrés Iniesta is a Spanish professional footballer who plays as a central midfielder for Barcelona and the Spain national team. He serves as the captain for Barcelona.Iniesta came through La Masia, the Barcelona youth academy, after an early emigration from his birthplace, and impressed from an early age. He made his first-team debut aged 18 in 2002. He began playing regularly during the 2004–05 season and has remained in the team ever since. Iniesta was an integral part of the Barcelona sides that won two historic trebles in 2009 and 2015, and his 33 trophies make him the most decorated Spanish footballer of all time.

</string>

    <string name="p38_info">
Luis Suárez commonly known as Luis Suárez, is a Uruguayan professional footballer who plays as a striker for Spanish club Barcelona and the Uruguay national team. Often regarded as one of the best players in the world,[nb 1] Suárez has won 14 trophies in his career, including four league titles, a UEFA Champions League title and a Copa América. A prolific goalscorer, Suárez has won two European Golden Shoes, an Eredivisie Golden Boot, a Premier League Golden Boot, as well as ending the six-year dominance of Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo by winning La Ligas Pichichi Trophy in 2016. In October 2015, he scored his 300th senior career goal for club and country.[10] Suárez notched his 400th goal two years later, in December 2017.

</string>

    <string name="p39_info">
Anderson Silva is a Brazilian mixed martial artist and former UFC Middleweight Champion. Silva held the longest title streak in UFC history, which ended in 2013 after 2,457 days, with 16 consecutive wins and 10 title defenses.[11] He has 13 post-fight bonuses, the second most in UFC history.[12] UFC president Dana White and several mixed-martial-arts publications have called Silva the greatest mixed martial artist of all time.[13][14][15][16][17][18] He is currently ranked the #6 contender in official UFC middleweight rankings.

</string>

    <string name="p40_info">
Paul Labile Pogba (born 15 March 1993) is a French professional footballer who plays for Premier League club Manchester United and the French national team. He operates primarily as a central midfielder and is comfortable playing both in attack and defence.After beginning his career with Manchester United in 2011, Pogba joined Italian side Juventus in 2012, and helped the club to four consecutive Serie A titles, as well as two Coppa Italia and two Supercoppa Italiana titles. During his time with the club, he established himself as one of the most promising young players in the world, and received the Golden Boy award in 2013, followed by the Bravo Award in 2014 and was named by The Guardian as one of the ten most promising young players in Europe. In 2016, Pogba was named to the 2015 UEFA Team of the Year as well as the 2015 FIFA FIFPro World XI, after helping Juventus to the 2015 UEFA Champions League Final. Despite leaving Manchester United on a free transfer, Pogba returned to the club in 2016 for a then-world record transfer fee of €105 million (£89.3 million).

</string>

    <string name="p41_info">
Carmelo Kyam Anthony is an American professional basketball player for the Oklahoma City Thunder of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Anthony attended Towson Catholic High School and Oak Hill Academy before playing college basketball at Syracuse. In Anthonys freshman season, he led the Orangemen to their first and only National Championship and was named the NCAA Tournaments Most Outstanding Player. Anthony then entered the 2003 NBA draft where he was selected with the third overall pick by the Denver Nuggets.

</string>

    <string name="p42_info">
Stanislas Wawrinka (French: [stanislas vav?i?ka]; born 28 March 1985) is a Swiss professional tennis player. Professionally known as Stan, he reached a career-high Association of Tennis Professionals (ATP) world No. 3 singles ranking for the first time on 27 January 2014.[2] His career highlights include three Grand Slam titles at the 2014 Australian Open, 2015 French Open and 2016 US Open, where he defeated the world No. 1 player in the final on all three occasions, reaching the final of the 2017 French Open, winning an ATP World Tour Masters 1000 title at the Monte-Carlo Masters in 2014, and reaching three other finals at 2008 Rome, 2013 Madrid and 2017 Indian Wells. He is sometimes considered as part of the newly-established "Big Five",[3][4] an expansion of the Big Four of Roger Federer, Rafael Nadal, Novak Djokovic and Andy Murray.

    </string>

    <string name="p43_info">
Dustin Johnson is an American professional golfer who currently plays on the PGA Tour. He is the current World Number 1 in the Official World Golf Ranking; having reached that position with his win at the 2017 Genesis Open in February 2017.[1] As of March 19 2018, he has been the Number 1-ranked golfer for 57 consecutive weeks, which is the 6th longest streak in PGA Tour history.He won the 2016 U.S. Open at Oakmont Country Club with a 4-under-par score of 276 for his first major championship. He had previously finished in a tie for second at both the 2011 Open Championship and the 2015 U.S. Open. He also has five World Golf Championships victories, with only Tiger Woods having won more, and he is the first player to win each of the four World Golf Championship events. He is one of the longest drivers on the PGA Tour, having been ranked in the top five annually from 2008 and leading in 2015.[2] By virtue of his 2018 Sentry Tournament of Champions win, Johnson became only the third player in Tour history to win a Tour title in each of his first 11 seasons, joining Jack Nicklaus (17) and Tiger Woods (14).
</string>

    <string name="p44_info">
Karim Benzema is a French professional footballer who plays as a striker for Spanish club Real Madrid and the France national team.[4] He has been described as an "immensely talented striker" who is "strong and powerful" and "a potent finisher from inside the box".[5]Benzema was born in the city of Lyon and began his football career with local club Bron Terraillon. In 1996, he joined Olympique Lyonnais, and subsequently came through the clubs youth academy. Benzema made his professional debut in the 2004–05 season and appeared sporadically in his first three seasons as Lyon won three titles in that span. In the 2007–08 season, Benzema became a starter and had a breakthrough year scoring over 30 goals as Lyon won its seventh straight league title. For his performances, he was named the National Union of Professional Footballers (UNFP) Ligue 1 Player of the Year and named to the organizations Team of the Year. Benzema was also the leagues top scorer and given the Bravo Award by Italian magazine Guerin Sportivo.
</string>

    <string name="p45_info">
Marcelo Vieira known as Marcelo (Portuguese pronunciation: [ma?s?lu]), is a Brazilian professional footballer for Spanish club Real Madrid and the Brazil national team. He plays mainly at left back but can also operate as a left winger.In 2005, he won a Campeonato Carioca with Fluminense and in 2006 he was named to the Brasileirão Team of the Season, at age 18. By the end of the year, he joined Real Madrid for a $8 million fee.[5] There he won three UEFA Champions Leagues, being elected to the Squad of the Season two times, as well as four La Liga titles.
</string>

    <string name="p46_info">
Radamel Falcao also known as Radamel Falcao, or simply Falcao, is a Colombian professional footballer who plays as a striker for Ligue 1 club AS Monaco, for whom he also serves as captain, and the Colombia national team. He is sometimes nicknamed "El Tigre" (Spanish for The Tiger) or "King of the Europa League".Falcao began his career at Lanceros Boyacá, before moving to Argentinian club River Plate where he won the 2007–08 Clausura tournament. In 2009, he joined Portuguese club Porto where he won several trophies, including the Europa League and Primeira Liga double in 2011. Falcao became their all-time top goalscorer in international club competitions and set the record for most goals (17) in a European campaign. He also became the first Colombian to receive the Portuguese Golden Ball award.[5] In August 2011, Falcao transferred to Atlético Madrid for a club record €40 million, leading them to Europa League and Super Cup victories in 2012.

</string>


    <string name="p47_info">
Cam Newton is an American football quarterback for the Carolina Panthers of the National Football League (NFL). He played college football at Auburn and was drafted as the first overall pick by the Panthers in the 2011 NFL Draft. Newton is the only player in the modern era to be awarded the Heisman Trophy, win a national championship, and become the first overall pick in an NFL draft within a one-year span.[3] He was the 2011 NFL Rookie of the Year, is a three-time Pro Bowler, and was named to the NFL All-Pro First Team in 2015.

</string>

    <string name="p48_info">
Simone Biles an American artistic gymnast. Biles is the 2016 Olympic individual all-around, vault and floor gold medalist, and balance beam bronze medalist. She was part of the gold medal-winning team dubbed the "Final Five" at the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro.Biles is a three-time world all-around champion (2013–15), three-time world floor champion (2013–15), two-time world balance beam champion (2014, 2015), four-time United States national all-around champion (2013–16), and a member of the gold medal-winning American teams at the 2014 and 2015 World Artistic Gymnastics Championships. She also won the bronze medal for vault at the 2015 World Championships.

</string>

    <string name="p49_info">
Sergio Agüero is an Argentine professional footballer who plays as a striker for Premier League club Manchester City and the Argentine national team.Agüero began his career at Independiente. On 5 July 2003, he became the youngest player to debut in the Argentine Primera División at 15 years and 35 days, breaking the record previously established by Diego Maradona in 1976. In 2006, Agüero moved to Europe to play for La Liga side Atlético Madrid, for a transfer fee of €23 million. He made a name for himself, attracting attention from Europes top clubs by scoring 101 goals in 234 appearances while winning the UEFA Europa League and the UEFA Super Cup in 2010.
</string>

    <string name="p50_info">
Ivan Rakitic is a Croatian professional footballer who plays as a central or attacking midfielder for Spanish club Barcelona and the Croatia national team.Rakitic started his professional career at Basel and spent two seasons with them before he was signed by Schalke 04. After spending three-and-a-half seasons in the Bundesliga, he was signed by Sevilla in January 2011. Two years later, Rakitic was confirmed as the club captain and captained the team to UEFA Europa League triumph. In June 2014, Barcelona and Sevilla reached an agreement on the transfer of Rakitic. In his first season with Barça, he won the treble of La Liga, Copa del Rey and UEFA Champions League. He scored the first goal of the 2015 Champions League Final and became the first player ever to win the Champions League one year after winning the Europa League while playing for two different clubs.
</string>

    <string name="p51_info">
Chris Paul is an American professional basketball player for the Houston Rockets of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He has won the NBA Rookie of the Year Award, an NBA All-Star Game Most Valuable Player Award, two Olympic gold medals, and led the NBA in assists four times and steals six times, being the all-time NBA leader in the latter category. He has also been selected to nine NBA All-Star teams, eight All-NBA teams, and nine NBA All-Defensive teams.

</string>

    <string name="p52_info">
Drew Brees is an American football quarterback for the New Orleans Saints of the National Football League (NFL). After a prolific college football career at Purdue University, he was chosen by the San Diego Chargers with the first pick in the second round of the 2001 NFL Draft. He left college as one of the most decorated players in Purdue and Big Ten Conference history, establishing two NCAA records, 13 Big Ten Conference records, and 19 Purdue University records. As of 2017, he remains the Big Ten record-holder in several passing categories, including completions (1,026), attempts (1,678), and yards (11,792).


</string>

    <string name="p53_info">
David Luiz known as David Luiz, is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays for English club Chelsea and the Brazil national team. Primarily a centre back, he can also be deployed as a defensive midfielder.After starting out at Vitória, he moved to Benfica, remaining with the club for five seasons (three complete). He joined Chelsea in January 2011, winning the UEFA Champions League, and the FA Cup during the 2011–12 season. In the following season he won the UEFA Europa League. In June 2014, he transferred to Paris Saint-Germain for a fee of £50 million, a world record transfer for a defender,[6][7][8] and won all four domestic competitions in both of his seasons in French football. He returned to Chelsea in August 2016 in a £30 million transfer deal.

</string>

    <string name="p54_info">
Cesc Fàbregas is a Spanish professional footballer who plays as a central midfielder for Premier League club Chelsea and the Spain national team.Fàbregas came through La Masia, Barcelonas youth academy, leaving at 16 when he was signed by Premier League club Arsenal in September 2003. Following injuries to key midfielders in the early part of the 2004–05 season, he went on establish himself in the team. He broke several of the clubs records in the process, earning a reputation as one of the best players in his position, and won the FA Cup in 2005. After a protracted transfer saga, Fàbregas left London on 15 August 2011 to return to Barcelona in a deal worth up to £35 million. During his three-year spell at the Camp Nou, Fàbregas played alongside Xavi and Andrés Iniesta and won a La Liga title, the Copa del Rey, the FIFA Club World Cup, the UEFA Super Cup and two Spanish Super Cups. He returned to London in June 2014 to Arsenals cross-town rivals Chelsea for a fee of £30 million, and in his first year there he helped to secure League Cup and Premier League triumphs.

</string>

    <string name="p55_info">
Russell Wilson is an American football quarterback for the Seattle Seahawks of the National Football League (NFL).
Wilson played college football for the University of Wisconsin during the 2011 season, in which he set the single-season FBS record for passing efficiency (191.8) and led the team to a Big Ten title and the 2012 Rose Bowl.[6] Wilson played football and baseball for North Carolina State University from 2008 to 2010 before transferring to Wisconsin. Wilson also played minor league baseball for the Tri-City Dust Devils in 2010 and the Asheville Tourists in 2011 as a second baseman.
</string>

    <string name="p56_info">
Aaron Charles Rodgers (born December 2, 1983) is an American football quarterback for the Green Bay Packers of the National Football League (NFL). Rodgers played college football for California, where he set several career passing records, including lowest single-season and career interception rates.[1] He was selected in the first round of the 2005 NFL Draft by the Packers.After backing up Brett Favre for the first three years of his NFL career, Rodgers became the Packers starting quarterback in 2008 and led them to a victory in Super Bowl XLV after the 2010 NFL season; Rodgers was named Super Bowl MVP. He was named Associated Press Athlete of the Year in 2011,[3] as well as being voted league MVP by the Associated Press for the 2011 and 2014 NFL seasons. Rodgers has led the NFL three times in touchdown-to-interception ratio (2011, 2012, 2014);[4] twice in passer rating (2011, 2012), touchdown passing percentage (2011, 2012), and lowest passing interception percentage (2009, 2014); and once in touchdown passes (2016) and yards per attempt (2011).

</string>


    <string name="p57_info">
Dani Alves commonly known as Dani Alves (Brazilian Portuguese: [d?~ni awvis]), is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a right back for French club Paris Saint-Germain and the Brazil national team. He serves as a 3rd captain for his club.
Before joining Barcelona in 2008, Alves spent a successful six-year spell with Sevilla, winning two UEFA Cups and the Copa del Rey with the Andalusian side. He joined Barcelona for €32.5 million,[3] becoming the third-most expensive defender of all-time. He won the treble in his first season with the club and in the next season, won the Supercopa de España, UEFA Super Cup and the FIFA Club World Cup. Additionally, he helped the club to clinch another two Supercopa de España, five La Liga titles and two UEFA Champions League titles in the years that followed. Alves has held a Spanish passport since 2005.[4] Alves is the second-most decorated defender of all-time in European competitions with nine European medals, leaving him one behind Paolo Maldini on the all-time list.

</string>

    <string name="p58_info">
Sergio Garcia is a Spanish professional golfer who plays on both the PGA Tour and the European Tour. García has won 31 international tournaments as a professional, most notably the 2008 Players Championship and the 2017 Masters Tournament.[2] Garcia is also the Chairman of Spanish football team CF Borriol.García has spent much of his career in the top 10 of the Official World Golf Ranking, including over 300 weeks in the top 10 between 2000 and 2009, and over 400 weeks in the top 10 in total.[3][4] García reached his highest career ranking, 2nd, after winning the HSBC Champions tournament in November 2008. García has achieved career earnings of more than US$43 million. As a player, he is noted for strong iron play and accuracy. In the Ryder Cup, García competed in eight of the nine matches playing during his professional career cumulatively earning 22.5 points during those matches.

</string>

    <string name="p59_info">
Manny Pacquiao is a Filipino professional boxer and politician, currently serving as a Senator of the Philippines.
He currently ranks #4 in BoxRecs ranking of the greatest pound for pound boxers of all time[2]. In 2016, Pacquiao was ranked number 2 on ESPNs list of top pound-for-pound boxers of the past 25 years.[3] He is the only eight-division world champion in the history of boxing,[4] having won eleven major world titles, as well as being the first boxer to win the lineal championship in five different weight classes.[5][6][7] Pacquiao is also the first boxer in history to win major world titles in four of the original eight weight classes of boxing: flyweight, featherweight, lightweight, and welterweight.

</string>

    <string name="p60_info">
Eli Manning is an American football quarterback for the New York Giants of the National Football League (NFL). He played college football at the University of Mississippi from 2000 to 2003. He was drafted as the first overall pick in the 2004 NFL Draft by the San Diego Chargers and was immediately traded to the Giants who in return gave up a package, highlighted by fourth overall selection Philip Rivers. Manning is the son of former NFL quarterback Archie Manning and the younger brother of former NFL quarterback Peyton Manning.Manning holds Giants franchise records for most passing yards, touchdown passes, and completed passes in a career,[2] and the NFL record for most fourth-quarter touchdown passes in a season. He led the Giants to victory in Super Bowls XLII and XLVI, defeating the New England Patriots in both games. Manning was named Most Valuable Player in each Super Bowl, becoming one of five players to have multiple Super Bowl MVP awards (Bart Starr and Terry Bradshaw also have two, Joe Montana three and Tom Brady four).

</string>

    <string name="p61_info">
Damian Lillard is an American professional basketball player for the Portland Trail Blazers of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He played college basketball for the Weber State Wildcats and earned third-team All-American honors in 2012. After being selected by Portland with the sixth overall pick in the 2012 NBA draft, Lillard won the NBA Rookie of the Year Award by unanimous decision. An NBA All-Star in 2014, 2015 and 2018, Lillard is one of six players in franchise history to become a three-time All-Star.

</string>

    <string name="p62_info">
Rickie Fowler is an American professional golfer who plays on the PGA Tour. He was the number one ranked amateur golfer in the world for 37 weeks in 2007 and 2008. On January 24, 2016 he reached a career high fourth in the Official World Golf Ranking following his victory in the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship.

    </string>

    <string name="p63_info">
Blake Griffin is an American professional basketball player for the Detroit Pistons of the National Basketball Association (NBA). He played college basketball for the Oklahoma Sooners, when he was named the Consensus National Player of the Year as a sophomore. Griffin was selected first overall by the Los Angeles Clippers in the 2009 NBA draft, and has since been a five-time NBA All-Star and a four-time All-NBA selection.Griffin won four high school state titles at Oklahoma Christian School under his father, head coach Tommy Griffin. Griffin played two seasons of college ball for the Sooners before entering the 2009 NBA draft, when he was selected by the Clippers. During the final pre-season game of 2009, he broke his left kneecap, had surgery, and missed the entire 2009–10 season.
</string>

    <string name="p64_info">
Odell Beckham Jr. is an American football wide receiver for the New York Giants of the National Football League (NFL). Born in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, Beckham played college football at nearby Louisiana State University (LSU), and was drafted by the Giants in the first round of the 2014 NFL Draft with the 12th overall pick. Since entering the NFL, Beckham has been one of the most productive and popular players, but he has drawn media scrutiny for his conduct on and off the playing field.

</string>

    <string name="p65_info">
Dwight Howard is an American professional basketball player for the Charlotte Hornets of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Howard, who plays center, spent his high school career at Southwest Atlanta Christian Academy. He chose to forgo college and entered the 2004 NBA draft, and was selected first overall by the Orlando Magic. An eight-time All-Star, eight-time All-NBA team selection, five-time All-Defensive member, and three-time Defensive Player of the Year, Howard has been ranked consistently as one of the best in the league in rebounds, blocks, field goal percentage and free throw attempts, and has set numerous franchise and league records. He led the Magic to three division titles and one conference title, and he was the winner of the 2008 NBA Slam Dunk Contest. In the 2008 Olympics, he was the starting center for Team USA, which went on to win the gold medal. He was traded to the Los Angeles Lakers in 2012, and signed with the Rockets in 2013.

</string>

    <string name="p66_info">
Ning Zetao is a Chinese competitive swimmer. Specializing in the freestyle, he won a gold medal in the 100 metre freestyle at the 2015 World Championships. At the 2014 Asian Games, he won gold medals in the 50 metre freestyle, 4 × 100 metre medley relay, 4 × 100 metre freestyle relay, and 100 metre freestyle, breaking the Asian records in the latter two events.[2][3][4] Ning also swam for China at the 2016 Summer Olympics.

</string>


    <string name="p67_info">
Ryan Lochte is an American competitive swimmer, a 12-time Olympic medalist (six gold, three silver, three bronze), which ranks him second in swimming behind Michael Phelps.[1] His seven individual Olympic medals rank near the top in mens swimming. As part of the American teams, he holds the world record in the 4×200-meter freestyle (long course) and 4x100-meter freestyle (mixed) relay. Individually, he currently holds the world record in the 200-meter individual medley (long and short course) and 400-meter individual medley (short course).

</string>

    <string name="p68_info">
Bastian Schweinsteiger is a German professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Major League Soccer club Chicago Fire. A right-footed player, he usually plays as central midfielder. Earlier in his career, he primarily played as a wide midfielder.He spent 13 seasons at Bayern Munich, playing in exactly 500 matches across all competitions and scoring 68 goals. His honours at the club include eight Bundesliga titles, seven DFB-Pokal titles, a UEFA Champions League title, a FIFA Club World Cup title and a UEFA Super Cup title.[4] He joined Manchester United in 2015, playing sparingly for 18 months before moving to Chicago Fire.
</string>

    <string name="p69_info">
Dale Earnhardt Jr. known professionally as Dale Earnhardt Jr., Dale Jr., or just Junior, is a retired American professional stock car racing driver, team owner, and is currently an analyst for NASCAR on NBC. He also competes part-time in the NASCAR Xfinity Series driving the No. 88 Chevrolet Camaro for his team JR Motorsports. He is the son of NASCAR Hall of Fame member Dale Earnhardt Sr. He is also the grandson of both NASCAR driver Ralph Earnhardt and stock car fabricator Robert Gee, the brother of Kelley Earnhardt-Miller, the half-brother of former driver Kerry Earnhardt, the uncle of driver Jeffrey Earnhardt, the stepson of Teresa Earnhardt, and the older half-brother of Taylor Nicole Earnhardt-Putnam.

</string>

    <string name="p70_info">
Javier Hernández is a Mexican professional footballer who plays as a striker for English club West Ham United and the Mexico national team. Hernández is commonly known by his nickname, Chicharito ([t?it?a?ito]; Mexican Spanish: little pea), which he wears on his shirt.He began his career in 2006, playing for the Mexican club Guadalajara, before becoming the first Mexican player to join Manchester United in July 2010. After falling out of favour under managers David Moyes and Louis van Gaal, he spent the 2014–15 season on loan to Real Madrid, then moved permanently to Bundesliga club Bayer Leverkusen in August 2015. His minutes-per-goal ratio during his time with Manchester United is among the most prolific in the history of the Premier League.

</string>

    <string name="p71_info">
Ma Long is a Chinese table tennis player.[1] The current Olympic and World Champion, he is ranked number 9 in the world (as of March 2018[4]) by the International Table Tennis Federation (ITTF). He has held the ranking of number 1 for a total of 64 months (and 34 consecutive months from March 2015), the most by any male player.[5] Ma was born in Anshan, Liaoning, China. He won a record total of 5 straight ITTF World Tour tournaments in a row, including a streak of 35 sets.

</string>

    <string name="p72_info">
Toni Kroos is a German professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Spanish club Real Madrid and the German national team.A member of Bayern Munichs first team at the age of 17, Kroos played in a 18-month loan spell at Bayer Leverkusen, before going back to Munich and winning back-to-back Bundesliga titles and the 2012–13 Champions League. After winning the FIFA World Cup in 2014, he joined Real Madrid on a six-year contract, for a fee of £20 million.[3] In Madrid, he won the 2015–16 and 2016–17 UEFA Champions Leagues and was elected to the Squad of the Season in the last four seasons. He became the first German to ever win three UCL titles.

</string>

    <string name="p73_info">
Justin Rose is an English professional golfer who plays most of his golf on the PGA Tour, while keeping his membership on the European Tour. He won his first major championship at the 2013 U.S. Open at Merion Golf Club, becoming the first English player to win a major since Nick Faldo in 1996 and the first to win the U.S. Open since Tony Jacklin in 1970. At the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro, Rose won gold at the mens individual tournament. With that victory, Rose joined Hall of Fame members Gary Player, David Graham, Hale Irwin and Bernhard Langer as one of only five golfers to win official tournaments on all six continents on which golf is played. Rose has also twice been runner-up at the Masters Tournament, in 2015 and 2017
</string>

    <string name="p74_info">
J.J. Watt is an American football defensive end for the Houston Texans of the National Football League (NFL). He was drafted by the Texans with the 11th pick in the first round of the 2011 NFL Draft, and played college football at Wisconsin.Watt received the AP NFL Defensive Player of the Year Award three times in his first five seasons.[1] Although primarily a defensive end, he occasionally shifts to defensive tackle in some situations. He has also taken snaps on offense, catching three touchdown passes during the 2014 season. In 2014, Watt became the first player in NFL history to record two 20+ sack seasons in a career.[2] He holds the Texans franchise records for both sacks and forced fumbles. In 2017, Sports Illustrated named Watt Sportsperson of the Year.

</string>

    <string name="p75_info">
Hope Solo is an American soccer goalkeeper, two-time Olympic gold medalist, and World Cup champion. She was the goalkeeper for the United States womens national soccer team from 2000 through August 2016. After playing at the collegiate level for the University of Washington, she played professionally for the Philadelphia Charge in the Womens United Soccer Association (WUSA). When the WUSA folded after her first season, she traveled to Europe to play for the top division leagues in Sweden and France. From 2009 to 2011, she played in the Womens Professional Soccer (WPS) for Saint Louis Athletica, Atlanta Beat and magicJack. After the WPS ceased operations in early 2012, she played for the Seattle Sounders in the W-League. She most recently played for Seattle Reign FC in the National Womens Soccer League, the top division of womens soccer in the United States.

</string>

    <string name="p76_info">
Thiago Silva commonly known as Thiago Silva, is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a central defender for and captains both Ligue 1 club Paris Saint-Germain and the Brazil national team.After moving to Europe to join Milan in 2009, Silva established himself as one of the highest rated defenders in the world, winning the Serie A title with the Rossoneri in the 2010–11 season. In July 2012, Paris Saint-Germain signed him for a reported €42 million, making him then the second-most expensive defender in history behind Rio Ferdinand.[3] With PSG, Silva has won four consecutive Ligue 1 championships, four consecutive Coupes de la Ligue and three consecutive Coupe de France.
</string>


    <string name="p77_info">
Raheem Sterling is a professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Premier League club Manchester City and the English national team. He received the Golden Boy award for 2014 from a pan-European panel of sports journalists, recognising him as the best under-21 player playing in Europe. A 2015 professional study by Soccerex ranked him as the most valuable young player in Europe, with a value of €49 million.Born in Jamaica, Sterling moved to London at the age of five and began his career at Queens Park Rangers before signing for Liverpool in 2010. In July 2015, following a lengthy dispute over a new contract, he was signed by Manchester City in a transfer potentially worth £49 million, the highest transfer fee ever paid for an English player.
</string>

    <string name="p78_info">
Eden Hazard is a Belgian professional footballer who plays for English club Chelsea and the Belgium national team. He primarily plays as an attacking midfielder and as a wide midfielder. Hazards creativity, speed, and technical ability are widely acknowledged.He has been described as "a superb passer" and has earned critical acclaim for his playing style, which has led to the media, coaches, and players drawing comparisons to Ballon dOr winners Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo. Hazard is often ranked by coaches, colleagues, and commentators as one of the best players in the world.

</string>

    <string name="p79_info">
Theo Walcott is an English professional footballer who plays as a forward for Premier League club Everton and the English national team.Walcott is a product of the Southampton Academy and started his career with Southampton before joining Arsenal for £5 million in 2006. His speedy pace and ball crossing led his manager Arsène Wenger to deploy him on the wing for most of his career. Walcott has been played as a striker since the 2012–13 season when he was Arsenals top scorer,and he has scored more than 100 goals for the club.
</string>

    <string name="p80_info">
Didier Drogba is an Ivorian professional footballer who plays as a striker for American club Phoenix Rising.[5] He is the all-time top scorer and former captain of the Ivory Coast national team. He is best known for his career at Chelsea, for whom he has scored more goals than any other foreign player and is currently the clubs fourth highest goal scorer of all time. He has been named African Footballer of the Year twice, winning the accolade in 2006 and 2009.After playing in youth teams, Drogba made his professional debut aged 18 for Ligue 2 club Le Mans, and signed his first professional contract aged 21. After finishing the 2002–03 season with 17 goals in 34 appearances for Ligue 1 side Guingamp, he moved to Olympique de Marseille, where he finished as the third highest scorer in the 2003–04 season with 19 goals and helped the club reach the 2004 UEFA Cup Final.
</string>

    <string name="p81_info">
Mario Götze ( born 3 June 1992) is a German professional footballer who plays as an attacking midfielder for Borussia Dortmund and the Germany national team. Although his favoured position is that of a playmaker, Götze also possesses speed, technique and dribbling skills. In 2010, German Football Associations then technical director Matthias Sammer described Götze as "one of the best talents Germany has ever had."
He played for Borussia Dortmund between 2009 and 2013, winning the Bundesliga title in 2010–11 and the Bundesliga and DFB-Pokal double in 2011–12, and was a member of the team which reached the 2013 UEFA Champions League Final. In April 2013, a €37 million bid from Bayern Munich triggered a release clause in Götzes contract, making Götze the second-most expensive German player to date, behind Mesut Özil.
Götze was first selected for the Germany national football team in 2010, at the age of 18. He was included in the squad for UEFA Euro 2012 and, two years later, scored the winning goal in the 2014 FIFA World Cup Final.
</string>

    <string name="p82_info">
Robert Lewandowski ( born 21 August 1988) is a Polish professional footballer who plays as a striker for Bundesliga club Bayern Munich and is the captain of the Poland national team.
After being the top scorer in the third and second tiers of Polish football with Znicz Pruszków, he moved to top-flight Lech Poznan, and was the top scorer in the league as they won the 2009–10 Ekstraklasa. In 2010, he transferred to Borussia Dortmund for a reported €4.5 million, where he won honours including two consecutive Bundesliga titles and a season as the leagues top goalscorer. In 2013, he earned with Borussia a spot in the 2013 UEFA Champions League Final, tournament where he was the second top goalscorer, behind only Cristiano Ronaldo.
Prior to the start of the 2014–15 season, Lewandowski agreed to join their rivals, Bayern Munich, on a free transfer.[3] In Munich, he won the Bundesliga title in each of his first three campaigns, earning a spot in the Bundesliga Team of the Year in every season. In 2015–16, he led the league in goalscoring with 30 goals, and in 2016–17 he was named the Bundesliga Player of The Year.[4][5] He was named to the UEFA Champions League Squad of the Season on each of the last two seasons.
    </string>

<string name="p83_info">
Marco Reus is a German professional footballer who plays as a forward for Borussia Dortmund and the Germany national team. He is renowned for his versatility, speed and technique,[3] but also for proneness to injury.
Reus spent his youth career at Borussia Dortmund, prior to leaving for Rot Weiss Ahlen. He has played for three clubs in his senior career, most notably—and with the most influence—in Borussia Dortmund of the Bundesliga.[10] Reus plays primarily as a left attacker for BVB; however, he is capable of playing on the right also and through the middle, due to his ability to closely control the ball with both feet.[citation needed] 2012 was his most successful season when, scoring 18 and assisting eight, he helped Borussia Mönchengladbach secure a place in the following seasons UEFA Champions League. Reus agreed a move to his home club Borussia Dortmund at the end of that season and is under contract at BVB until 2023.[11] Reus wears the number 11 shirt for Dortmund.With Dortmund, Reus won the 2013 DFL-Supercup and the German Cup in 2017. Reus was the Footballer of the Year in Germany in 2012 and was on the UEFA Team of the Year in 2013. In 2012, Franz Beckenbauer spoke about Reus, along with Mario Götze, saying, "...[A]s a classic duo there is nobody better than the prolific Reus and Götze."[12] In 2013, Reus was ranked as the fourth best footballer in Europe by Bloomberg.

</string>

    <string name="p84_info">
Lewis Carl Davidson Hamilton MBE (born 7 January 1985) is a British racing driver who races in Formula One for the Mercedes AMG Petronas team. A four-time Formula One World Champion, he is often considered the best driver of his generation and widely regarded as one of the greatest Formula One drivers in the history of the sport.[note 1] He won his first World Championship title with McLaren in 2008, then moved to Mercedes where he won back-to-back titles in 2014 and 2015 before winning his fourth title in 2017. Statistically the most successful British driver in the history of the sport, Hamilton has won more World Championship titles (4) and more race victories than any other British driver in Formula One (62). He also holds records for the all-time most career points (2,610), the most wins at different circuits (24), the all-time most pole positions (72) and the most grand slams in a season.


</string>

    <string name="p85_info">
Jason Day (born 12 November 1987) is an Australian professional golfer and PGA Tour member. He is a former World Number 1 in the World Golf Ranking, having first achieved the ranking in September 2015. Day first broke into the worlds top ten in June 2011, rising to world number nine after his runner-up finish at the U.S. Open.[4] In February 2014, Day won his first WGC title, the WGC-Accenture Match Play Championship and would win it for a second time in 2016. With his 2016 win, he joined Tiger Woods and Geoff Ogilvy as the only multiple winners of the WGC Match Play. He went on to win his first major tournament at the 2015 PGA Championship, scoring a record 20 strokes under par and rising to number three in the world rankings.


</string>

    <string name="p86_info">
Jimmie Kenneth Johnson (born September 17, 1975) is an American professional stock car racing driver and a seven-time champion in the Monster Energy NASCAR Cup Series. He currently drives the No. 48 Chevrolet Camaro ZL1 for Hendrick Motorsports.
Johnson was born in El Cajon, California, and began racing motorcycles at the age of four. After graduating from Granite Hills High School he competed in off-road series. He raced in Mickey Thompson Entertainment Group (MTEG), Short-course Off-road Drivers Association (SODA) and SCORE International, winning rookie of the year in each series. In 1998, Johnson and his team, Herzog Motorsports, began stock car racing. He moved to the national American Speed Association (ASA) series for late model touring cars, and won another rookie of the year title. In 2000, he switched to the NASCAR Busch Series
Winning the Malaysian Open in 2017 marked Lins success in having won every major title in the badminton world.


</string>


    <string name="p87_info">
Caroline Wozniacki ( born 11 July 1990) is a Danish professional tennis player. She is currently world No. 2 and a former world No. 1 in singles in the WTA Tour. [10][11] She was the first woman from a Scandinavian country to hold the top ranking position and 20th overall.She finished on top of the rankings in both 2010 and 2011. Wozniacki won her first Grand Slam title at the 2018 Australian Open and returned to the No. 1 ranking on 29 January 2018.
She has won 28 WTA singles titles, including six in 2010 and 2011, the most in a year by a WTA player from 2008–2011.She was runner-up at the 2009 US Open and the 2010 WTA Tour Championships to Kim Clijsters, and at the 2014 US Open to Serena Williams. She won the 2006 Wimbledon Girls Singles title and also holds two WTA titles in doubles. In 2008, Wozniacki won the title of WTA Newcomer of the Year. In 2017, Wozniacki won the season-ending WTA Finals in Singapore for the first time in her career.



</string>

    <string name="p88_info">
Lin Dan is a Chinese professional badminton player. He is a two-time Olympic champion, five-time World champion, as well as a six-time All England champion.
Widely regarded as the greatest badminton player of all time,by the age of 28 Lin had completed the "Super Grand Slam", having won all nine major titles in the badminton world: Olympic Games, World Championships, World Cup, Thomas Cup, Sudirman Cup, Super Series Masters Finals, All England Open, Asian Games, and Asian Championships, becoming the first and only player to achieve this feat.[6][7] He also became the first mens singles player to retain the Olympic gold medal by winning in 2008 and defending his title in 2012.


</string>

    <string name="p89_info">
Santos Saúl Álvarez Barragán is a Mexican professional boxer. He has held multiple world championships in two weight classes, including the Ring magazine middleweight title since 2015. Previously he had two reigns as light middleweight world champion, holding the WBA (Unified), WBC, and Ring titles between 2011 and 2013, and the WBO title from 2016 to 2017. At middleweight he also held the WBC and lineal titles between 2015 and 2017.
As of February 2018, Álvarez is ranked as the worlds best active boxer, pound for pound, by BoxRec;fourth by the Transnational Boxing Rankings Board (TBRB) and ESPN;[4] and fifth by The Ring.[5] He is also ranked as the worlds best active middleweight by BoxRec,and fourth by the TBRB

</string>

    <string name="p90_info">
Yuvraj Singh is an Indian international cricketer, who plays all forms of the game. An all-rounder who bats left-handed in the middle order and bowls slow left-arm orthodox, Yuvraj is the son of former Indian fast bowler and Punjabi actor Yograj Singh.
Yuvraj has been a member of the Indian cricket team in ODIs since October 2000 and played his first Test match in October 2003. He was the vice-captain of the Indian ODI team between 2007–2008. He was the Man of the Tournament in the 2011 ICC Cricket World Cup, and one of the top performers at the 2007 ICC World Twenty20, both of which India won. In a match against England at the 2007 World Twenty20, he famously hit six sixes in one over bowled by Stuart Broad — a feat performed only three times previously in any form of senior cricket, and never in an international match between two Test cricket teams. In the same match, he set the record for the fastest fifty in Twenty20 Internationals and in all Twenty20 cricket, reaching 50 runs in 12 balls. During the 2011 World Cup, he became the first player to take a 5-wicket haul and score a 50 in the same World Cup match.

</string>

    <string name="p91_info">
Thomas Müller is a German professional footballer who plays for and vice-captains Bayern Munich and the German national team. A versatile player, Müller plays as a midfielder or forward, and has been deployed in a variety of attacking roles – as an attacking midfielder, second striker, centre forward and on either wing. He has been praised for his positioning, teamwork and stamina, work-rate, and has shown consistency in both scoring and creating goals.

A product of Bayerns youth system, he made his first-team breakthrough in the 2009–10 season after Louis van Gaal was appointed as the main coach; he played almost every game as the club won the league and cup double and reached the Champions League final. Müller scored 23 goals in the 2012–13 season as Bayern won a historic treble; the league title, cup and Champions League.


</string>

    <string name="p92_info">
Felipe Massa (born 25 April 1981) is a Brazilian former Formula One racing driver. Massa started his career in go-karting from the age of eight continuing in national and regional championships for seven years. He moved into Formula Chevrolet and claimed the championship. He moved in Italian Formula Renault in 2000 and won the title along with the European championship. Massa went into Euro Formula 3000 taking the championship.

Massa started his Formula One career with Sauber before joining Scuderia Ferrari as a test driver for 2003. He returned to Sauber for 2004 and 2005 before rejoining Ferrari where he won two races in 2006 including his home Grand Prix becoming the first Brazilian since Ayrton Senna to win the Brazilian Grand Prix. Massa won three races in 2007, finishing 4th in the Drivers Championship. He finished second in the 2008 Drivers World Championship after a long title battle with Lewis Hamilton, winning six races to Hamiltons five. At the 2009 Hungarian Grand Prix, Massa was injured by a suspension spring off the Brawn GP car of Rubens Barrichello. Massa was forced to miss the rest of the season but returned in 2010. Massa suffered a dip in form in 2011 scoring no podiums but consistently scoring points. Massa contributed to Ferraris Constructors Championships in 2007 and 2008 and was under contract to race for the team until the end of the 2013 season. On 10 September 2013, he confirmed he would be leaving Ferrari at the end of the 2013 season.


</string>
    <string name="p93_info">
Eugenie "Genie" Bouchard ( born February 25, 1994) is a Canadian professional tennis player. At the 2014 Wimbledon Championships, Bouchard became the first Canadian-born player representing Canada[a] to reach the finals of a Grand Slam in singles, finishing runner-up to Petra Kvitová.[3] She also reached the semifinals of the 2014 Australian Open[4] and 2014 French Open,[5] and won the 2012 Wimbledon girls title.[6] Following the end of the 2013 WTA Tour, she was named WTA Newcomer of the Year.[7][8] The next year, Bouchard received the WTA Most Improved Player award for the 2014 season and reached a career-high ranking of No. 5, becoming the first Canadian female tennis player to be ranked in the top 5 in singles.[9]
Since having to withdraw with concussion prior to her 4th round match at the 2015 US Open, Bouchard has neither reached the fourth round of a Grand Slam nor won a title on tour. Due to her struggles, her ranking in January 2018 dropped out of the top 100 for the first time since April 2013.

</string>

    <string name="p94_info">
Gerry Lester "Bubba" Watson Jr.[1][2] (born November 5, 1978) is an American professional golfer who plays on the PGA Tour. One of the few left-handed golfers on tour, he is a multiple major champion, having won the Masters Tournament in 2012 and 2014.[3] In February 2015, Watson reached a career-high 2nd place in the Official World Golf Ranking.
Watson is among the longest drivers on the PGA Tour; in 2007 he had an average drive of 315.2 yards (288.2 m) and can hit a ball over 350 yards (320 m), capable of generating a ball speed up to 194 mph (312 km/h).[4][5] He has finished top of the driving distance statistics five times in his career, during the 2006, 2007, 2008, 2012 and 2014 PGA Tour seasons.

    </string>

    <string name="p95_info">
Suresh Kumar Raina (About this sound pronunciation (help·info); born 27 November 1986) is an Indian professional cricketer. An aggressive left-handed middle-order batsman and an occasional off-spinbowler, he is considered as one of the best fielders in world cricket. He plays for Uttar Pradesh in all forms of domestic cricket. He was the captain of Gujarat Lions in the Indian Premier League, and is the vice-captain of the Chennai Super Kings.[1] He has also captained the Indian cricket team and is the second-youngest player ever to captain India. He is the first of the three Indian batsmen to ever score a century in all three formats of international cricket.
Raina made his ODI debut in July 2005 against Sri Lanka at the age of 19. However, his Test debut came about five years later, in July 2010, against the same opposition. He scored a hundred on his Test debut. He was a part of the Indian squad that won the 2011 World Cup.


</string>

    <string name="p96_info">
Gabriel Fernando de Jesus (born 3 April 1997)is a professional footballer who plays as a forward for Premier League club Manchester City and the Brazil national team.
Jesus began his career at Palmeiras. He was voted the best newcomer of the 2015 Campeonato Brasileiro Série A, a year in which he also helped his team win the Copa do Brasil. The following year he was named the player of the season as Palmeiras won their first national league title in 22 years. He joined Premier League club Manchester City in January 2017 for a transfer fee of €32 million.
Jesus has represented Brazil youth teams at the 2015 FIFA U-20 World Cup, where they reached the final, and at the 2016 Summer Olympics, as they defeated Germany in the final.[5] He made his senior debut for Brazil in September 2016.
In 2014, Neuer finished third in the voting, behind Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo, for the FIFA Ballon dOr award. The same year, he was ranked the third-best player in the world by The Guardian.



</string>

<string name="p97_info">
Manuel Peter Neuer ( born 27 March 1986) is a German professional footballer who plays as a goalkeeper for and captains both Bundesliga club Bayern Munich and the Germany national team. Neuer has been described as a "sweeper-keeper" because of his unique playing style and speed when rushing off his line to anticipate opponents;[4][5][6] he is also known for his quick reflexes, excellent shot-stopping abilities, strength, long throwing range, command of his area and accurate control and distribution of the ball.
Regarded by pundits as the best goalkeeper in the world (he won the IFFHS Worlds Best Goalkeeper award for four consecutive years between 2013 and 2016),[11][12][13][14][15] and as one of the best and most complete goalkeepers of all-time,[14][16][17] Neuer won the 2014 FIFA World Cup with Germany as well as the Golden Glove award for being the best goalkeeper in the tournament,[18] and is considered by some in the sport to be the best goalkeeper in football since Lev Yashin.
</string>

<string name="p98_info">
Adam Derek Scott (born 16 July 1980) is an Australian professional golfer who plays mainly on the PGA Tour. He was the World No. 1 ranked golfer, from mid-May to August 2014.[2] He has won 29 professional tournaments around the world (3 being unofficial money events), on many of golfs major tours. His biggest win to date was the 2013 Masters Tournament, his first major championship and the first Masters won by an Australian in its history.[3] Other significant wins include the 2004 Players Championship, the 2011 WGC-Bridgestone Invitational and the 2016 WGC-Cadillac Championship. He was the runner-up in the 2012 Open Championship, leading by four strokes with four holes to play before bogeying all of them to lose the title by a stroke to Ernie Els.
</string>

<string name="p99_info">
Born	May 25, 1994 (age 23)
Alexandra Rose Raisman (born May 25, 1994) is an American gymnast and two-time Olympian. She was a member and captain of both the 2012 "Fierce Five" and 2016 "Final Five" U.S. womens Olympic gymnastics which won their respective team competitions. Raisman is the 2016 Olympic individual all-around silver medalist and floor silver medalist.
At the 2012 Olympics in London, she won gold medals in the team and floor competitions, as well as the bronze medal on the balance beam, making her the most decorated American gymnast at the Games. At the 2016 Olympics in Rio de Janeiro, she won a gold medal in the team event, making her and teammate Gabby Douglas the only Americans with back-to-back team gold medals. Raisman also won silver medals in the individual all-around and for floor exercise.
Raisman was also a member of the gold-winning American teams at the 2011 and 2015 World Championships.
</string>

<string name="p100_info">
Mohamed Salah Ghaly (born 15 June 1992) is an Egyptian professional footballer who plays as a forward for Liverpool and the Egyptian national team.
Salah started his career with El Mokawloon then transferred to FC Basel in 2012, then he played for Chelsea, Fiorentina (on loan) and for Roma before transferring to Liverpool in 2017. As well as representing the Egyptian national team since 2011, He won a bronze medal in Africa U-20 Cup of Nations, he also participated in the 2011 FIFA U-20 World Cup, the 2012 Summer Olympics, 2017 CAF Cup of Nations and he reached the final but lost it, then he qualified with his national team to the FIFA World Cup 2018 and he became the top scorer of FIFA World Cup qualification (CAF).
</string>







<!-- //********************************  Sports INFO **************************************************************/  -->
    <string name="s1_info">
Archery is the sport, practice or skill of using a bow to propel arrows. The word comes from the Latin arcus. Historically, archery has been used for hunting and combat. In modern times, it is mainly a competitive sport and recreational activity. A person who participates in archery is typically called an archer or a bowman, and a person who is fond of or an expert at archery is sometimes called a toxophilite
</string>

    <string name="s2_info">
Athletics is a collection of sporting events that involve competitive running, jumping, throwing, and walking.[1] The most common types of athletics competitions are track and field, road running, cross country running, and race walking.
The results of racing events are decided by finishing position (or time, where measured), while the jumps and throws are won by the athlete that achieves the highest or furthest measurement from a series of attempts. The simplicity of the competitions, and the lack of a need for expensive equipment, makes athletics one of the most commonly competed sports in the world. Athletics is mostly an individual sport, with the exception of relay races and competitions which combine athletes performances for a team score, such as cross country.

    </string>


    <string name="s3_info">
Badminton is a racquet sport played using racquets to hit a shuttlecock across a net. Although it may be played with larger teams, the most common forms of the game are "singles" (with one player per side) and "doubles" (with two players per side). Badminton is often played as a casual outdoor activity in a yard or on a beach; formal games are played on a rectangular indoor court. Points are scored by striking the shuttlecock with the racquet and landing it within the opposing sides half of the court.
Each side may only strike the shuttlecock once before it passes over the net. Play ends once the shuttlecock has struck the floor or if a fault has been called by the umpire, service judge, or (in their absence) the opposing side.[1]
The shuttlecock is a feathered or (in informal matches) plastic projectile which flies differently from the balls used in many other sports. In particular, the feathers create much higher drag, causing the shuttlecock to decelerate more rapidly. Shuttlecocks also have a high top speed compared to the balls in other racquet sports. The flight of the shuttlecock gives the sport its distinctive nature.


</string>

    <string name="s4_info">
Basketball is a limitedcontact sport played on a rectangular court. While most often played as a team sport with five players on each side, threeonthree, twoontwo, and oneonone competitions are also common. The objective is to shoot a basketball (approximately 9.4 inches (24 cm) in diameter) through a hoop 18 inches (46 cm) in diameter and 10 feet (3.048 m) high that is mounted to a backboard at each end of the court. The game was invented in 1891 by Dr. James Naismith.
A team can score a field goal by shooting the ball through the basket being defended by the opposition team during regular play. A field goal scores three points for the shooting team if the player shoots from behind the threepoint line, and two points if shot from in front of the line. A team can also score via free throws, which are worth one point, after the other team is assessed with certain fouls. The team with the most points at the end of the game wins, but additional time (overtime) is mandated when the score is tied at the end of regulation. The ball can be advanced on the court by passing it to a teammate, or by bouncing it while walking or running (dribbling). It is a violation to lift, or drag, ones pivot foot without dribbling the ball, to carry it, or to hold the ball with both hands then resume dribbling.
The game has many individual techniques for displaying skill—ballhandling, shooting, passing, dribbling, dunking, shotblocking, and rebounding. Basketball teams generally have player positions, the tallest and strongest members of a team are called a center or power forward, while slightly shorter and more agile players are called small forward, and the shortest players or those who possess the best ball handling skills are called a point guard or shooting guard. The point guard directs the on court action of the team, implementing the coachs game plan, and managing the execution of offensive and defensive plays (player positioning).

</string>

    <string name="s5_info">
Beach volleyball is a team sport played by two teams of two players on a sand court divided by a net. As in indoor volleyball, the objective of the game is to send the ball over the net and to ground it on the opponents court, and to prevent the same effort by the opponent. A team is allowed up to three touches to return the ball across the net. The ball is put in play with a serve—a hit by the server from behind the rear court boundary over the net to the opponents. The rally continues until the ball is grounded on the playing court, goes "out", or is not returned properly.[1][2] The team winning a rally scores a point and serves to start the following rally. The four players serve in the same sequence throughout the match, changing server each time a rally is won by the receiving team.
Beach volleyball most likely originated in 1915 on Waikiki Beach in Hawaii, while the modern twoman game originated in Santa Monica, California. It has been an Olympic discipline since the 1996 Games. The Fédération Internationale de Volleyball (FIVB) is the international governing body for the sport, and organizes the FIVB Beach Volleyball World Championships and the international professional beach volleyball circuit known as the FIVB Beach Volleyball World Tour.
</string>

    <string name="s6_info">
Boxing is a combat sport in which two people, usually wearing protective gloves, throw punches at each other for a predetermined set of time in a boxing ring.

Amateur boxing is both an Olympic and Commonwealth Games sport and is a common fixture in most international games—it also has its own World Championships. Boxing is supervised by a referee over a series of one to threeminute intervals called rounds. The result is decided when an opponent is deemed incapable to continue by a referee, is disqualified for breaking a rule, resigns by throwing in a towel, or is pronounced the winner or loser based on the judges scorecards at the end of the contest. In the event that both fighters gain equal scores from the judges, the fight is considered a draw (professional boxing). In Olympic boxing, due to the fact that a winner must be declared, in the case of a draw  the judges use technical criteria to choose the most deserving winner of the bout.
While humans have fought in handtohand combat since before the dawn of history, boxing as an organized sport may have its origin in the ancient Greeks as an Olympic game in 688 BC. Boxing evolved from 16th and 18thcentury prizefights, largely in Great Britain, to the forerunner of modern boxing in the mid19th century with the 1867 introduction of the Marquess of Queensberry Rules.

</string>


    <string name="s7_info">
Canoe slalom (previously known as whitewater slalom) is a competitive sport with the aim to navigate a decked canoe or kayak through a course of hanging downstream or upstream gates on river rapids in the fastest time possible. It is one of the two kayak and canoeing disciplines at the Summer Olympics, and is referred to by the International Olympic Committee (IOC) as Canoe/Kayak Slalom. The other Olympic canoeing discipline is canoe sprint. Wildwater canoeing is a nonOlympic paddlesport.Each gate consists of two poles hanging from a wire strung across the river. There are 1825 numbered gates in a course, of which 67 must be upstream gates, and they are colored as either green (downstream) or red (upstream), indicating the direction they must be negotiated. Upstream gates are always placed in eddies, where the water is flat or moving slightly upstream; the paddler enters an eddy from the main current and paddles upstream through the gate. Downstream gates may also be placed in eddies, to increase the difficulty, and downstream gates in the current can be offset to alternating sides of the current, requiring rapid turns in fastmoving water.
Most slalom courses take 80 to 120 seconds to complete for the fastest paddlers. Depending on the level of competition, difficulty of the course, degree of water turbulence. and ability of the other paddlers, times can go up to 200 seconds.
In international competitions (World Cups, World Championships, Olympic Games) each competitor does two runs in the qualification round, called the "heats"; the time of the faster run gives the qualification result. Depending on the number of participants in the event, 10 to 40 boats make it through to the semifinal; this consists of one run on a different course. The fastest semifinal boats, the number determined by the number of participants, make it through to the final, where they navigate the semifinal course once more. Their ranking within the final group is based on the time of that last run alone.[2]
If the competitors boat, paddle or body touches either pole of the gate, a time penalty of two seconds is added. If the competitor misses a gate completely, deliberately pushes the gate to pass through, goes through the gate in the wrong direction or upsidedown, or goes through it in the wrong order, a 50second penalty is given. Only one penalty can be incurred on each gate, and this will be taken as the highest one.

</string>

    <string name="s8_info">
Canoe sprint is a sport in which athletes race canoes or kayaks on calm water.

Race categories vary by the number of athletes in the boat, the length of the course, and whether the boat is a canoe or kayak. Canoe sprints are sometimes referred to as flat water racing. The distances recognized by the ICF for international canoe sprint races are 200m, 500m, and 1000m. These races take place on straight courses with each boat paddling in its own designated lane. Longer marathon races do exist, notably the 5000m (also an ICFrecognized distance)  these usually have athletes starting in a large pack at a start line before paddling around a set course with marked turning points (there are no assigned lanes). For each race a number of heats, semifinals and a final may be necessary, depending on the number of competitors.

The sport is governed by the International Canoe Federation. The International Canoe Federation is the worldwide canoeing organization and creates the standard rules for the different disciplines of canoe/kayak competition. The ICF recognizes several competitive and noncompetitive disciplines of canoeing, of which Sprint and Slalom are the only two competing in the Olympic games. National organizations include the United States Canoe Association, the British Canoe Union (now British Canoeing, Singapore Canoe Federation, Croatian Canoe Federation, Australian Canoeing, and the Pakistan Canoe and Kayak Federation.

On the whole, Europe has dominated the sport, winning over 90 per cent of all available medals.[1]

The official boats recognized by the ICF as International Boats are: K1, K2, K4, C1, C2 and C4, where the number indicates the number of paddlers, “K” stands for kayak and “C” for canoe.[2] The ICF rules for these boats define, among others, the maximum length, the minimum weight and the shape of the boats  for instance, a K1 must be 520 cm long and weighs at least 8 kg for marathons or 12 kg for sprints. Originally, width (beam) restrictions were also enforced; these were revoked in 2000, spurring a flurry of innovations in boat designs. Modern boats are usually made of carbon fiber, aramid fiber (e.g., Kevlar) with epoxy resin, or variants of highperformance fiberglass.


</string>

    <string name="s9_info">
BMX, an abbreviation for bicycle motocross or bike motocross, is a cycle sport performed on BMX bikes, either in competitive BMX racing or freestyle BMX, or else in general on or offroad recreation. BMX began when young cyclists appropriated motocross tracks for fun, racing and stunts, eventually evolving specialized BMX bikes and competitionsBMX began during the early 1970s in the United States when children began racing their bicycles on dirt tracks in southern California, inspired by the motocross stars of the time. The size and availability of the Schwinn StingRay and other wheelie bikes made them the natural bike of choice for these races, since they were easily customized for better handling and performance. BMX racing was a phenomenon by the mid1970s. Children were racing standard road bikes offroad, around purposebuilt tracks in California.[1] The 1972 motorcycle racing documentary On Any Sunday is generally credited with inspiring the movement nationally in the United States; its opening scene shows kids riding their StingRays offroad. By the middle of that decade, the sport achieved critical mass, and manufacturers began creating bicycles designed especially for the sport.

</string>

    <string name="s10_info">
Track cycling is a bicycle racing sport usually held on specially built banked tracks or velodromes (but many events are held at older velodromes where the track banking is relatively shallow) using track bicycles.Track cycling has been around since at least 1870. When cycling was in its infancy, wooden indoor tracks were laid which resemble those of modern velodromes, consisting of two straights and slightly banked turns.

One appeal of indoor track racing was that spectators could be easily controlled, and hence an entrance fee could be charged, making track racing a lucrative sport. Early track races attracted crowds of up to 2000 people. Indoor tracks also enabled yearround cycling for the first time. The main early centers for track racing in Britain were Birmingham, Sheffield, Liverpool, Manchester and London.

The most noticeable changes in over a century of track cycling have concerned the bikes themselves, engineered to be lighter and more aerodynamic to enable everfaster times.

With the exception of the 1912 Olympics, track cycling has been featured in every modern Olympic Games. Womens track cycling was first included in the modern Olympics in 1988.
</string>

    <string name="s11_info">
cycling mountain bike
Mountain biking is the sport of riding bicycles offroad, often over rough terrain, using specially designed mountain bikes. Mountain bikes share similarities with other bikes but incorporate features designed to enhance durability and performance in rough terrain. Mountain biking can generally be broken down into multiple categories: cross country, trail riding, all mountain (also referred to as "Enduro"), downhill, freeride and dirt jumping. However, the majority of mountain biking falls into the categories of Trail and Cross Country riding styles.

The sport requires endurance, core strength and balance, bike handling skills, and selfreliance. Advanced riders pursue both steep technical descents and high incline climbs. In the case of freeride, downhill, and dirt jumping, aerial maneuvers are performed off both natural features and specially constructed jumps and ramps.

Mountain bikers ride on offroad trails such as singletrack, backcountry roads, fire roads, and often venture to ski resorts that stay open in the summer for such activities. Because riders are often far from civilization, there is a strong ethic of selfreliance in the sport. Riders learn to repair broken bikes and flat tires to avoid being stranded. Many riders carry a backpack, including water, food, tools for trailside repairs, and a first aid kit in case of injury. Group rides are common, especially on longer treks. Mountain bike orienteering adds the skill of map navigation to mountain biking.

</string>

    <string name="s12_info">
Road cycling is the most widespread form of cycling. It includes recreational, racing, and utility cycling. Road cyclists are generally expected to obey the same rules and laws as other vehicle drivers or riders and may also be vehicular cyclists.Dedicated road bicycles have drop handlebars and multiple gears, although there are single and fixed gear varieties. Road bikes also use narrow, highpressure tires to decrease rolling resistance, and tend to be somewhat lighter than other types of bicycle. The drop handlebars are often positioned lower than the saddle in order to put the rider in a more aerodynamic position. In an effort to become more aerodynamic, some riders have begun using aerobars.[1] Who and when aerobars where invented is unclear but they seem to date back to the early 1980s.[2] The light weight and aerodynamics of a road bike allows this type of bicycle to be the second most efficient selfpowered means of transportation, behind only recumbent bicycles due to the latters higher aerodynamic efficiency.


</string>


    <string name="s13_info">
Track cycling is a bicycle racing sport usually held on specially built banked tracks or velodromes (but many events are held at older velodromes where the track banking is relatively shallow) using track bicycles.Track cycling has been around since at least 1870. When cycling was in its infancy, wooden indoor tracks were laid which resemble those of modern velodromes, consisting of two straights and slightly banked turns.

One appeal of indoor track racing was that spectators could be easily controlled, and hence an entrance fee could be charged, making track racing a lucrative sport. Early track races attracted crowds of up to 2000 people. Indoor tracks also enabled yearround cycling for the first time. The main early centers for track racing in Britain were Birmingham, Sheffield, Liverpool, Manchester and London.

The most noticeable changes in over a century of track cycling have concerned the bikes themselves, engineered to be lighter and more aerodynamic to enable everfaster times.

With the exception of the 1912 Olympics, track cycling has been featured in every modern Olympic Games. Womens track cycling was first included in the modern Olympics in 1988.

</string>

    <string name="s14_info">
Dressage (/dr?s???/ or /dr?s???/; a French term, most commonly translated to mean "training") is a highly skilled form of riding performed in exhibition and competition, as well as an "art" sometimes pursued solely for the sake of mastery. As an equestrian sport defined by the International Equestrian Federation, dressage is "the highest expression of horse training" where "horse and rider are expected to perform from memory a series of predetermined movements.Competitions are held at all levels from amateur to the Olympic Games and World Equestrian Games. Its fundamental purpose is to develop, through standardized progressive training methods, a horses natural athletic ability and willingness to perform, thereby maximizing its potential as a riding horse. At the peak of a dressage horses gymnastic development, the horse responds smoothly to a skilled riders minimal aids. The rider is relaxed and appears effortfree while the horse willingly performs the requested movement.

The discipline has a rich history with ancient roots in the writings of Xenophon. Modern dressage has evolved as an important equestrian pursuit since the Renaissance when Federico Grisones "The Rules of Riding" was published in 1550, the first treatise on equitation in over a thousand years since Xenophons On Horsemanship.[2] Much about training systems used today reflects practices of classical dressage.

In modern dressage competition, successful training at the various levels is demonstrated through the performance of "tests", prescribed series of movements ridden within a standard arena. Judges evaluate each movement on the basis of an objective standard appropriate to the level of the test and assign each movement a score from zero to ten – zero being "not executed" and 10 being "excellent". A score of 9 is very good and is a high mark, while a competitor achieving all 6s (or 60% overall) should be considering moving on to the next level.

    </string>

    <string name="s15_info">
Eventing (also known as three day eventing or horse trials) is an equestrian event where a single horse and rider combination compete against other combinations across the three disciplines of dressage, crosscountry, and show jumping. This event has its roots in a comprehensive cavalry test which required mastery of several types of riding. The competition may be run as a oneday event (ODE), where all three events are completed in one day (dressage, followed by cross country and then stadium) or a threeday event (3DE), which is more commonly now run over four days, with dressage on the first two days followed by cross country the next day and then show jumping in reverse order on the final day. Eventing was previously known as Combined Training, and the name persists in many smaller organizations. The term "Combined Training" is sometimes confused with the term "Combined Test" which refers to a combination of just two of the phases, most commonly dressage and show jumping.

</string>

    <string name="s16_info">
Show jumping, also known as "stadium jumping", "open jumping", or simply "jumping", is a part of a group of English riding equestrian events that also includes dressage, eventing, hunters, and equitation. Jumping classes are commonly seen at horse shows throughout the world, including the Olympics. Sometimes shows are limited exclusively to jumpers, sometimes jumper classes are offered in conjunction with other Englishstyle events, and sometimes show jumping is but one division of very large, allbreed competitions that include a very wide variety of disciplines. Jumping classes may be governed by various national horse show sanctioning organizations, such as the United States Equestrian Federation in the USA or the British Showjumping Association in Great Britain. International competitions are governed by the rules of the International Federation for Equestrian Sports (FEI, from the bodys French name of Fédération Équestre Internationale)

</string>

    <string name="s17_info">
Fencing is a group of three related combat sports. The three disciplines in modern fencing are the foil, the épée, and the sabre; winning points are made through the contact with an opponent. A fourth discipline, singlestick, appeared in the 1904 Olympics but was dropped after that, and is not a part of modern fencing. Fencing was one of the first sports to be played in the Olympics. Based on the traditional skills of swordsmanship, the modern sport arose at the end of the 19th century, with the Italian school having modified the historical European martial art of classical fencing, and the French school later refining the Italian system. There are three forms of modern fencing, each uses a different kind of weapon and has different rules, this way the sport itself is divided into three competitive scenes: foil, épée, and sabre. Most competitive fencers choose to specialize in one weapon only.

Competitive fencing is one of the five activities which have been featured in every modern Olympic Games, the other four being athletics, cycling, swimming, and gymnastics.
</string>

    <string name="s18_info">
Football is a family of team sports that involve, to varying degrees, kicking a ball with a foot to score a goal. Unqualified, the word football is understood to refer to whichever form of football is the most popular in the regional context in which the word appears. Sports commonly called football in certain places include: association football (known as soccer in some countries); gridiron football (specifically American football or Canadian football); Australian rules football; rugby football (either rugby league or rugby union); and Gaelic football.[1][2] These different variations of football are known as football codes.

Various forms of football can be identified in history, often as popular peasant games. Contemporary codes of football can be traced back to the codification of these games at English public schools during the nineteenth century.[3][4] The expanse of the British Empire allowed these rules of football to spread to areas of British influence outside the directly controlled Empire.[5] By the end of the nineteenth century, distinct regional codes were already developing: Gaelic football, for example, deliberately incorporated the rules of local traditional football games in order to maintain their heritage.[6] In 1888, The Football League was founded in England, becoming the first of many professional football competitions. During the twentieth century, several of the various kinds of football grew to become some of the most popular team sports in the world.[7]

</string>


    <string name="s19_info">
Golf is a clubandball sport in which players use various clubs to hit balls into a series of holes on a course in as few strokes as possible.

Golf, unlike most ball games, cannot and does not utilize a standardized playing area, and coping with the varied terrains encountered on different courses is a key part of the game. The game at the highest level is played on a course with an arranged progression of 18 holes, though recreational courses can be smaller, usually 9 holes. Each hole on the course must contain a tee box to start from, and a putting green containing the actual hole or cup (4.25 inches in diameter). There are other standard forms of terrain in between, such as the fairway, rough (long grass), sand traps (or "bunkers"), and various hazards (water, rocks, fescue) but each hole on a course is unique in its specific layout and arrangement.

Golf is played for the lowest number of strokes by an individual, known as stroke play, or the lowest score on the most individual holes in a complete round by an individual or team, known as match play. Stroke play is the most commonly seen format at all levels, but most especially at the elite level.

The modern game of golf originated in 15th century Scotland. The 18hole round was created at the Old Course at St Andrews in 1764. Golfs first major, and the worlds oldest tournament in existence, is The Open Championship, also known as the British Open, which was first played in 1860 in Ayrshire, Scotland. This is one of the four major championships in mens professional golf, the other three being played in the United States: The Masters, the U.S. Open, and the PGA Championship.

</string>

    <string name="s20_info">
The rings, also known as steady rings or still rings[1] (in contrast to flying rings), is an artistic gymnastics apparatus and the event that uses it. It is traditionally used only by male gymnasts, due to its extreme upperbody strength requirements. Gymnasts typically wear ring grips while performing on the rings.

The apparatus consists of two rings that hang freely from a rigid metal frame. Each ring is supported by a strap, which in turn connects to a steel cable that is suspended from the metal frame. The gymnast, who grips one ring with each hand, must control the movement of the rings and his or her body movements during all time.

</string>

    <string name="s21_info">
Rhythmic gymnastics is a sport in which individuals or groups of five or more manipulate one or two pieces of apparatus: rope, hoop, ball, clubs, ribbon and freehand (no apparatus). Rhythmic gymnastics is a sport that combines elements of ballet, gymnastics, dance, and apparatus manipulation. The victor is the participant who earns the most points, determined by a panel of judges, for leaps, balances, pirouettes (pivots), apparatus handling, and execution. The choreography must cover the entire floor and contain a balance of jumps, leaps, pivots, balances (a certain number is required depending on the gymnasts level) and flexibility movements. Each movement involves a high degree of athletic skill. Physical abilities needed by a rhythmic gymnast include strength, power, flexibility, agility, dexterity, endurance and handeye coordination.

The sport is governed by the Federation Internationale de Gymnastique (FIG), which designs the Code of Points and regulates all aspects of international elite competition. The largest events in the sport are the Olympic Games, World Championships, European Championships, World Cup and GrandPrix Series.


</string>

    <string name="s22_info">
Handball (also known as team handball, European handball or Olympic handball)[1] is a team sport in which two teams of seven players each (six outfield players and a goalkeeper) pass a ball using their hands with the aim of throwing it into the goal of the other team. A standard match consists of two periods of 30 minutes, and the team that scores more goals wins.

Modern handball is played on a court 40 by 20 metres (131 by 66 ft), with a goal in the middle of each end. The goals are surrounded by a 6meter (20 ft) zone where only the defending goalkeeper is allowed; goals must be scored by throwing the ball from outside the zone or while "diving" into it. The sport is usually played indoors, but outdoor variants exist in the forms of field handball and Czech handball (which were more common in the past) and beach handball. The game is fast and highscoring: professional teams now typically score between 20 and 35 goals each, though lower scores were not uncommon until a few decades ago. Body contact is permitted by the defenders trying to stop the attackers from approaching the goal.

The game was codified at the end of the 19th century in northern Europe. The modern set of rules was published in 1917 in Germany, and had several revisions since. The first international games were played under these rules for men in 1925 and for women in 1930. Mens handball was first played at the 1936 Summer Olympics in Berlin as outdoors, and the next time at the 1972 Summer Olympics in Munich as indoors, and has been an Olympic sport since. Womens team handball was added at the 1976 Summer Olympics.

The International Handball Federation was formed in 1946 and, as of 2016, has 197 member federations.[2] The sport is most popular in the countries of continental Europe, which have won all medals but one in the mens world championships since 1938. In the womens world championships, only two nonEuropean countries have won the title: South Korea and Brazil. The game also enjoys popularity in the Far East, North Africa and parts of South America.


</string>

    <string name="s23_info">
Hockey is a sport in which two teams play against each other by trying to maneuver a ball or a puck into the opponents goal using a hockey stick. There are many types of hockey such as bandy, field hockey and ice hockey.

Often one variation of the sport, such as field hockey or ice hockey, will predominate in a certain area and be known simply as "hockey.Games played with curved sticks and a ball can be found in the histories of many cultures. In Egypt, 4000yearold carvings feature teams with sticks and a projectile, hurling dates to before 1272 BC in Ireland, and there is a depiction from approximately 600 BC in Ancient Greece, where the game may have been called keretízein or (?e??t??e??) because it was played with a horn or hornlike stick (kéras, ???a?).[5] In Inner Mongolia, the Daur people have been playing beikou, a game similar to modern field hockey, for about 1,000 years.[6]

Most evidence of hockeylike games during the Middle Ages is found in legislation concerning sports and games. The Galway Statute enacted in Ireland in 1527 banned certain types of ball games, including games using "hooked" (written "hockie", similar to "hooky") sticks.[7]

...at no tyme to use ne occupye the horlinge of the litill balle with hockie stickes or staves, nor use no hande ball to play withoute walles, but only greate foote balle[8]

By the 19th century, the various forms and divisions of historic games began to differentiate and coalesce into the individual sports defined today. Organizations dedicated to the codification of rules and regulations began to form, and national and international bodies sprang up to manage domestic and international competition


    </string>

    <string name="s24_info">
Judo (?? judo, meaning "gentle way") was created as a physical, mental and moral pedagogy in Japan, in 1882, by Jigoro Kano (?????). It is generally categorized as a modern martial art which later evolved into a combat and Olympic sport. Its most prominent feature is its competitive element, where the objective is to either throw or takedown an opponent to the ground, immobilize or otherwise subdue an opponent with a pin, or force an opponent to submit with a joint lock or a choke. Strikes and thrusts by hands and feet as well as weapons defenses are a part of judo, but only in prearranged forms (kata, ?) and are not allowed in judo competition or free practice (randori, ???). A judo practitioner is called a judoka.

The philosophy and subsequent pedagogy developed for judo became the model for other modern Japanese martial arts that developed from koryu (??, traditional schools).

</string>

    <string name="s25_info">
Marathon swimming is a class of open water swimming defined by long distances (at least 10 kilometers) and traditional rules based in English Channel swimming. Unlike marathon footraces which have a specifically defined distance, marathon swims vary in distance. However, one commonly used minimum definition is 10 kilometers, the distance of the marathon swimming event at the Olympic Games.[1]

As in all open water swimming, tides, surface currents and windchop are major determinants of finishtimes. For a given course, these factors can vary dramatically from day to day, making any attempt to draw conclusions about athletic ability by comparing finish times from performances undertaken on different days meaningless.

One of the earliest marathon swims was accomplished in 1875 by Captain Matthew Webb, when he became the first person to swim across the English Channel. Similarly, perhaps the most famous marathon swim of alltime was accomplished in 1926 by Gertrude Ederle, when she became, at 19 years of age, the first woman to swim across the English Channel. In doing so, she demolished the existing world record for the crossing, by employing the crawl stroke technique.

The Triple Crown of Open Water Swimming includes three of the most wellknown marathon swims: (1) 21 mi (34 kilometres) across the English Channel, (2) 20.1 mi (32.3 kilometres) between Catalina Island and the mainland in Southern California, USA, and (3) 28.5 mi (45.9 kilometres) around Manhattan Island in New York City, USA.

The Oceans seven is a collection of seven channel swims: (1) North Channel between Ireland and Scotland, (2) Cook Strait between the North and South Islands of New Zealand, (3) Molokai Channel between Oahu and Molokai Islands in Hawaii, (4) English Channel between England and France, (5) Catalina Channel between Santa Catalina Island and Southern California, (6) Tsugaru Strait between the islands of Honshu and Hokkaido in Japan, and (7) Strait of Gibraltar between Europe and Africa. Irish swimmer Steve Redmond became the first person to complete the Oceans seven upon completing the Tsugaru Strait on May 15, 2012


</string>

    <string name="s26_info">
The modern pentathlon is an Olympic sport that comprises five different events; fencing (onetouch épée), freestyle swimming (200m), equestrian show jumping (15 jumps), and a final combined event of pistol shooting and cross country running (3200m). This last event is now referred to as the laserrun, since it alternates four legs of laser pistol shooting followed by an 800m run (for 3200m in total). The event is inspired by the traditional pentathlon held during the ancient Olympics; as the original events were patterned on the skills needed by an ideal Greek soldier of the era, the modern pentathlon is similarly patterned on events representing the skills needed by cavalry behind enemy lines.

The sport has been a core sport of the Olympic Games since 1912 despite attempts to remove it.[1] A world championships for modern pentathlon has been held annually since 1949.

Originally the competition took place over four or five days; in 1996 a oneday format was adopted in an effort to be more audiencefriendly.[2] Modern pentathlon, despite its long Olympic history, has had to justify its inclusion in the modern Olympic Games several times. On February 11, 2013 in Lausanne, the IOC confirmed modern pentathlon once again as one of the 25 core sports of the Olympic program through to 2020. The governing body, Union Internationale de Pentathlon Moderne (UIPM), administers the international sport in more than 90 countries in all the continents of the world.

</string>

    <string name="s27_info">
Rowing is the act of propelling a boat using the motion of oars in the water, displacing water, and propelling the boat forward. The difference between paddling and rowing is that rowing requires oars to have a mechanical connection with the boat, while paddles are handheld and have no mechanical connection.

This article deals with the more general types of rowing, such as for recreation and transport rather than the sport of competitive rowing which is a specialized case of racing using strictly regulated equipment and a highly refined technique.

</string>


    <string name="s28_info">
Rugby football usually refers to rugby union or sometimes rugby league, which are both team sports, rugby union originating at Rugby School in Rugby, Warwickshire, and rugby league originating in Huddersfield, West Yorkshire after splitting and forming the Northern Union in 1896 (what is now known as rugby league). The first rugby match in North America was played between McGill University and Harvard University. The champion of the match between both McGill and Harvard received the Covo cup. Rugby football (both league and union) is one of many versions of football played at English public schools in the 19th century, along with association football.[1]. Although rugby league initially used rugby union rules, they are now wholly separate sports. In addition to the two existing codes, both codes of Gridiron football (American football and Canadian football) have evolved from rugby football, but themselves also completely different sports altogether

</string>

    <string name="s29_info">
Sailing employs the wind—acting on sails, wingsails or kites—to propel a craft on the surface of the water (sailing ship, sailboat, windsurfer, or kitesurfer), on ice (iceboat) or on land (land yacht) over a chosen course, which is often part of a larger plan of navigation.

A course defined with respect to the true wind direction is called a point of sail.

Conventional sailing craft cannot derive power from sails on a point of sail that is too close into the wind. On a given point of sail, the sailor adjusts the alignment of each sail with respect to the apparent wind direction (as perceived on the craft) to mobilize the power of the wind. The forces transmitted via the sails are resisted by forces from the hull, keel, and rudder of a sailing craft, by forces from skate runners of an iceboat, or by forces from wheels of a land sailing craft to allow steering the course.

In the 21st century, most sailing represents a form of recreation or sport. Recreational sailing or yachting can be divided into racing and cruising. Cruising can include extended offshore and oceancrossing trips, coastal sailing within sight of land, and daysailing.

Until the mid of the 19th century, sailing ships were the primary means for marine commerce, this period is known as Age of Sail.


</string>

    <string name="s30_info">
Shooting is the act or process of discharging projectiles from a ranged weapon such as guns, bows or crossbows and slingshots. Even the discharging/launching of artillery, darts, grenades, rockets and guided missiles can be called shooting. When using a firearm, the act of shooting is often called firing.

Shooting can take place in a shooting range or in the field, in shooting sports, hunting or in combat. A person who is involved in the shooting activity is a shooter, and those proficient in shooting is called a marksman or sharpshooter. The level of a persons shooting skills is referred to as marksmanship
</string>

    <string name="s31_info">
Swimming is the selfpropulsion of a person through fresh or salt water, usually for recreation, sport, exercise, or survival. Locomotion is achieved through coordinated movement of the limbs, the body, or both. Humans can hold their breath underwater and undertake rudimentary locomotive swimming within weeks of birth, as an evolutionary response.[1]

Swimming is consistently among top public recreational activities,[2][3][4][5] and in some countries, swimming lessons are a compulsory part of the educational curriculum.[6] As a formalized sport, swimming features in a range of local, national, and international competitions, including every modern summer Olympics


</string>

    <string name="s32_info">
Synchronised swimming (renamed as artistic swimming since July 2017 by the global governing body FINA),[1][2] is a hybrid form of swimming, dance, and gymnastics, consisting of swimmers performing a synchronised routine (either solo, duet, mixed duet, free team, free combination, and highlight) of elaborate moves in the water, accompanied by music.

Synchronised swimming demands advanced water skills, requires great strength, endurance, flexibility, grace, artistry and precise timing, as well as exceptional breath control when upside down underwater. During routines swimmers may not touch the bottom of the pool.

Following the addition of a new mixedpair event, FINA World Aquatics competitions are open to men since the 16th 2015 championships in Kazan, and the other international, national and provincial/state competitions allow male competitors in every event. However, men are currently still barred from competing in the Olympics. Both USA Synchro and Synchro Canada allow men to compete with women. Most European countries allow men to compete, France even allows male only podiums, according to the number of participants. In the past decade more men are becoming involved in the sport and a global biannual competition called Mens Cup has been steadily growing.

Competitors show off their strength, flexibility, and aerobic endurance required to perform difficult routines. Swimmers perform two routines for the judges, one technical and one free, as well as age group routines and figures.

Synchronised swimming is both an individual and team sport. Swimmers compete individually during figures, and then as a team during the routine. Figures are made up of a combination of skills and positions that often require control, strength, and flexibility. Swimmers are ranked individually for this part of the competition. The routine involves teamwork and synchronisation. It is choreographed to music and often has a theme.

Synchronised swimming is governed internationally by FINA (Fédération Internationale de Natation).



    </string>

    <string name="s33_info">
Table tennis, also known as ping pong, is a sport in which two or four players hit a lightweight ball back and forth across a table using small bats. The game takes place on a hard table divided by a net. Except for the initial serve, the rules are generally as follows: players must allow a ball played toward them to bounce one time on their side of the table, and must return it so that it bounces on the opposite side at least once. A point is scored when a player fails to return the ball within the rules. Play is fast and demands quick reactions. Spinning the ball alters its trajectory and limits an opponents options, giving the hitter a great advantage.

Table tennis is governed by the worldwide organization International Table Tennis Federation (ITTF), founded in 1926. ITTF currently includes 226 member associations.[3] The table tennis official rules are specified in the ITTF handbook.[4] Table tennis has been an Olympic sport since 1988,[5] with several event categories. From 1988 until 2004, these were mens singles, womens singles, mens doubles and womens doubles. Since 2008, a team event has been played instead of the doubles.


</string>

    <string name="s34_info">
Taekwondo (UK: /?ta?kw?ndo?/,[1] /?ta?kw?ndo?/,[2] US: /ta?kw?ndo?/;[3] from Korean ??? [t??.k?w?n.do] (About this sound listen)) is a Korean martial art, characterized by its emphasis on headheight kicks, jumping and spinning kicks, and fast kicking techniques.

Taekwondo was developed during the 1940s and 1950s by Korean martial artists with experience in martial arts such as karate, Chinese martial arts, and indigenous Korean martial arts traditions such as Taekkyeon, Subak, and Gwonbeop.[4][5] The oldest governing body for taekwondo is the Korea Taekwondo Association (KTA), formed in 1959 through a collaborative effort by representatives from the nine original kwans, or martial arts schools, in Korea. The main international organizational bodies for taekwondo today are the International TaekwonDo Federation (ITF), founded by Choi Hong Hi in 1966, and the partnership of the Kukkiwon and World Taekwondo (WT, formerly WTF), founded in 1972 and 1973 respectively by the Korea Taekwondo Association. Gyeorugi ([kj??ugi]), a type of fullcontact sparring, has been an Olympic event since 2000. The governing body for taekwondo in the Olympics and Paralympics is World Taekwondo.


</string>

    <string name="s35_info">
Tennis is a racket sport that can be played individually against a single opponent (singles) or between two teams of two players each (doubles). Each player uses a tennis racket that is strung with cord to strike a hollow rubber ball covered with felt over or around a net and into the opponents court. The object of the game is to play the ball in such a way that the opponent is not able to play a valid return. The player who is unable to return the ball will not gain a point, while the opposite player will.

Tennis is an Olympic sport and is played at all levels of society and at all ages. The sport can be played by anyone who can hold a racket, including wheelchair users. The modern game of tennis originated in Birmingham, England, in the late 19th century as lawn tennis.[1] It had close connections both to various field (lawn) games such as croquet and bowls as well as to the older racket sport today called real tennis. During most of the 19th century, in fact, the term tennis referred to real tennis, not lawn tennis: for example, in Disraelis novel Sybil (1845), Lord Eugene De Vere announces that he will "go down to Hampton Court and play tennis."[2]

The rules of modern tennis have changed little since the 1890s. Two exceptions are that from 1908 to 1961 the server had to keep one foot on the ground at all times, and the adoption of the tiebreak in the 1970s. A recent addition to professional tennis has been the adoption of electronic review technology coupled with a pointchallenge system, which allows a player to contest the line call of a point, a system known as HawkEye.

Tennis is played by millions of recreational players and is also a popular worldwide spectator sport. The four Grand Slam tournaments (also referred to as the Majors) are especially popular: the Australian Open played on hard courts, the French Open played on red clay courts, Wimbledon played on grass courts, and the US Open also played on hard courts.


</string>

    <string name="s36_info">
A trampoline is a device consisting of a piece of taut, strong fabric stretched between a steel frame using many coiled springs. People bounce on trampolines for recreational and competitive purposes.

The fabric that users bounce on (commonly known as the "bounce mat" or "trampoline bed") is not elastic itself; the elasticity is provided by the springs that connect it to the frame, which store potential energy.


</string>


    <string name="s37_info">
A triathlon is a multiplestage competition involving the completion of three continuous and sequential endurance disciplines.[1] While many variations of the sport exist, triathlon, in its most popular form, involves swimming, cycling, and running in immediate succession over various distances. Triathletes compete for fastest overall course completion time, including timed "transitions" between the individual swim, cycle, and run components.[1] The word "triathlon" is of Greek origin from t?e?? or treis ("three") and ????? or athlos ("competition").[2]

A transition area is set up where the athletes change gear for different segments of the race. This is where the switches from swimming to cycling and cycling to running occur. These areas are used to store bicycles, performance apparel, and any other accessories needed for the next stage of the race. The transition from swim to bike is referred to as T1 and that between the bike and run is referred to as T2. The athletes overall time for the race includes time spent in T1 and T2.[3] Transition areas vary in size depending on the number of participants expected. In addition, these areas provide a social headquarters before the race.[4]

The nature of the sport focuses on persistent and often periodized training in each of the three disciplines, as well as combination workouts and general strength conditioning.[5]



</string>

    <string name="s38_info">
Volleyball is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other teams court under organized rules.[1] It has been a part of the official program of the Summer Olympic Games since 1964.

The complete rules are extensive, but simply, play proceeds as follows: a player on one of the teams begins a rally by serving the ball (tossing or releasing it and then hitting it with a hand or arm), from behind the back boundary line of the court, over the net, and into the receiving teams court. The receiving team must not let the ball be grounded within their court. The team may touch the ball up to 3 times but individual players may not touch the ball twice consecutively. Typically, the first two touches are used to set up for an attack, an attempt to direct the ball back over the net in such a way that the serving team is unable to prevent it from being grounded in their court.

The rally continues, with each team allowed as many as three consecutive touches, until either (1): a team makes a kill, grounding the ball on the opponents court and winning the rally; or (2): a team commits a fault and loses the rally. The team that wins the rally is awarded a point, and serves the ball to start the next rally. A few of the most common faults include:

causing the ball to touch the ground or floor outside the opponents court or without first passing over the net;
catching and throwing the ball;
double hit: two consecutive contacts with the ball made by the same player;
four consecutive contacts with the ball made by the same team;
net foul: touching the net during play;
foot fault: the foot crosses over the boundary line when serving.
The ball is usually played with the hands or arms, but players can legally strike or push (short contact) the ball with any part of the body.

A number of consistent techniques have evolved in volleyball, including spiking and blocking (because these plays are made above the top of the net, the vertical jump is an athletic skill emphasized in the sport) as well as passing, setting, and specialized player positions and offensive and defensive structures.


</string>

    <string name="s39_info">
Water polo is a competitive team sport played in the water between two teams. The game consists of four quarters, usually of eight minutes, in which the two teams attempt to score goals and throw the ball into their opponents goal. The team with the most goals at the end of the game wins the match. Each team is made up of six field players and one goalkeeper. Except for the goalkeeper, players participate in both offensive and defensive roles. the goal keeper is allowed to use 2 hands at all times. Water polo is typically played in an alldeep pool seven feet (or two meters) deep.

Special equipment for water polo includes a water polo ball, which floats on the water; numbered and coloured caps; and two goals, which either float in the water or are attached to the side of the pool.

The game is thought to have originated in Scotland in the late 19th century as a sort of "water rugby". William Wilson is thought to have developed the game during a similar period. The game thus developed with the formation of the London Water Polo League and has since expanded, becoming widely popular in various places around the world, including Europe, the United States, Brazil, China, Canada and Australia.



</string>

    <string name="s40_info">
Weightlifting, also called Olympicstyle weightlifting, or Olympic weightlifting, is an athletic discipline in the modern Olympic programme in which the athlete attempts a maximumweight single lift of a barbell loaded with weight plates.

The two competition lifts in order are the snatch and the clean and jerk. The snatch is a wide grip one move lift. The Clean and Jerk is a close grip two move lift. Each weightlifter receives three attempts in each, and the combined total of the highest two successful lifts determines the overall result within a bodyweight category. Bodyweight categories are different for male and female competitors. A lifter who fails to complete at least one successful snatch and one successful clean and jerk also fails to total, and therefore receives an "incomplete" entry for the competition. The clean and press was once a competition lift, but was discontinued due to difficulties in judging proper form.

In comparison with other strength sports, which test limit strength (with or without lifting aids), weightlifting tests aspects of human ballistic limits (explosive strength); the lifts are therefore executed faster—and with more mobility and a greater range of motion during their execution—than other strength movements. Properly executed, the snatch and the clean and jerk are both dynamic and explosive while appearing graceful, especially when viewed from a recording at a slowed speed.

While there are relatively few competitive Olympic weightlifters, the lifts performed in the sport of weightlifting, and in particular their component lifts (e.g. squats, deadlifts, cleans), are commonly used by elite athletes in other sports to train for both explosive and functional strength.



</string>
    <string name="s41_info">
Freestyle wrestling is a style of amateur wrestling that is practiced throughout the world. Along with GrecoRoman, it is one of the two styles of wrestling contested in the Olympic games. American high school and college wrestling is conducted under different rules and is termed scholastic and collegiate wrestling.

Freestyle wrestling, like collegiate wrestling, has its greatest origins in catchascatchcan wrestling and, in both styles, the ultimate goal is to throw and pin the opponent to the mat, which results in an immediate win. Freestyle and collegiate wrestling, unlike GrecoRoman, allow the use of the wrestlers or his opponents legs in offense and defense. Freestyle wrestling brings together traditional wrestling, judo, and sambo techniques.

According to wrestlings world governing body, United World Wrestling (UWW), freestyle wrestling is one of the four main forms of amateur competitive wrestling that are practiced internationally today. The other main forms of wrestling are GrecoRoman and grappling (also called submission wrestling). The Executive Board of the International Olympic Committee (IOC) recommended dropping wrestling as a sport from the 2020 Olympic Games, but the decision was later reversed by the IOC.



</string>
    <string name="s42_info">
GrecoRoman (US) or GraecoRoman (UK) wrestling is a style of wrestling that is practiced worldwide. It was contested at the first modern Olympic Games in 1896 and has been included in every edition of the summer Olympics held since 1908.[2] Two wrestlers are scored for their performance in two threeminute periods, which can be terminated early by a pin (or fall). This style of wrestling forbids holds below the waist; this is the major difference from freestyle wrestling, the other form of wrestling at the Olympics. This restriction results in an emphasis on throws because a wrestler cannot use trips to take an opponent to the ground, or avoid throws by hooking or grabbing the opponents leg.

Arm drags, bear hugs, and headlocks, which can be found in Freestyle, have even greater prominence in GrecoRoman. In particular, a throw known as a suplex is used, in which the offensive wrestler lifts his opponent in a high arch while falling backward on his own neck to a bridge in order to bring his opponents shoulders down to the mat. Even on the mat, a GrecoRoman wrestler must still find several ways to turn his opponents shoulders to the mat for a fall without legs, including techniques known as the bodylock and the gutwrench.[3]

According to United World Wrestling, GrecoRoman wrestling is one of the six main forms of amateur competitive wrestling practised internationally today. The other five forms are Freestyle wrestling, Grappling/Submission wrestling, Beach wrestling, Pankration athlima, Alysh/Belt wrestling and Traditional/Folk wrestling.[4]

</string>
    <!-- //********************************  SPORTS INFO END **************************************************************/  -->











    <!-- //********************************  SPORTS RULES **************************************************************/  -->

    <string name="s1_rules">
Rules of Archery

Archers must adhere to all official rules in terms of the equipment they use in the performance of their sport, with the main emphasis being on them using no equipment or accessories that would give an unfair advantage over an opponent.
The maximum time permitted to shoot an end of three arrows is two minutes, and four minutes for an end of six arrows.
Athletes may not raise the bow arm until the signal to start is given and penalties can be given – in the form of points forfeits – if the bow is drawn after the official practice has been closed.
An arrow cannot be reshot under any circumstances. The arrow may be considered not to have been shot if it falls from the bow or misfires, or if the target blows or falls over. Extra time would be given in such circumstances.
An arrow that rebounds or hangs from the target will still score based on the mark it makes on the target face. Arrows that stick – Robin Hoodstyle – in the nock of another shall score the same as the arrow in which they are embedded.
Athletes can be disqualified, have points deducted or be banned from competition for various breaches of rules, based on the severity of the offence.
If equipment is damaged, appeals can be made to the judge for such equipment to be replaced or fixed, and any time allowances will be at the judge’s discretion.
</string>

    <string name="s2_rules">
Rules of Athletics

Each individual discipline has its own specific set of rules and competitors are expected to abide by these to ensure that the competition is fair.
</string>

    <string name="s3_rules">
Rules of Badminton

A game can take place with either two (singles) or four (doubles) players.
An official match has to be played indoors on the proper court dimensions. The dimensions are 6.1m by 13.4m, The net is situated through the middle of the court and is set at 1.55m.
To score a point the shuttlecock must hit within the parameters of the opponents court.
If the shuttlecock hits the net or lands out then a point is awarded to your opponent.
Players must serve diagonally across the net to their opponent. As points are won then serving stations move from one side to the other. There are no second serves so if your first serve goes out then your opponent wins the point.
A serve must be hit underarm and below the servers waist. No overarm serves are allowed.
Each game will start with a toss to determine which player will serve first and which side of the court the opponent would like to start from.
Once the shuttlecock is ‘live’ then a player may move around the court as they wish. They are permitted to hit the shuttlecock from out of the playing area.
If a player touches the net with any part of their body or racket then it is deemed a fault and their opponent receives the point.
A fault is also called if a player deliberately distracts their opponent, the shuttlecock is caught in the racket then flung, the shuttlecock is hit twice or if the player continues to infract with the laws of badminton.
Each game is umpired by a referee on a high chair who overlooks the game. There are also line judges who monitor if the shuttlecock lands in or not. The referee has overriding calls on infringements and faults.
Let may be called by the referee if an unforeseen or accidental circumstance arose. These may include the shuttlecock getting stuck in the bet, server serving out of turn, one player was not ready or a decision which is too close to call.
The game has only two rest periods coming the form of a 90 second rest after the first game and a 5 minute rest period after the second game.
If the laws are continuously broken by a player then the referee holds the power to dock that player of points with persisting fouls receiving a forfeit of the set or even the match.
</string>

    <string name="s4_rules">
Rules of Basketball
Each team can have a maximum of 5 players on the court at any one time. Substitutions can be made as many times as they wish within the game.
The ball can only be moved by either dribbling (bouncing the ball) or passing the ball. Once a player puts two hands on the ball (not including catching the ball) they cannot then dribble or move with the ball and the ball must be passed or shot.
After the ball goes into a team’s half and they win possession back the ball must then make it back over the half way line within 10 seconds. If the ball fails to do so then a foul will be called and the ball will be turned over.
Each team has 24 seconds to at least shot at the basket. A shot constitutes either going in the basket or hitting the rim of the basket. If after the shot is taken and the ball fails to go in the basket then the shot clock is restarted for another 24 seconds.
The team trying to score a basket is called the offence whilst the team trying to prevent them from scoring is called the defence. The defence must do all they can to stop the offence from scoring by either blocking a shot or preventing a shot from being fired.
After each successful basket the ball is then turned over to the opposition.
Fouls committed throughout the game will be accumulated and then when reached a certain number will be eventually be awarded as a free throw. A free throw involves one playerfrom the offensive team (the player fouled) to take a shot unopposed from the free throw line. Depending on where the foul was committed will depend on the number free throws a player gets.
Violations in basketball include travelling (taking more than one step without bouncing the ball), double dribble (picking the ball up dribbling, stopping then dribbling again with two hands), goaltending (a defensive player interferes with the ball travelling downwards towards the basket) and back court violation (once the ball passes the half way line the offensive team cannot take the ball back over the half way line).
</string>

    <string name="s5_rules">
Rules of Beach Volley Ball
As a court sport, Beach Volleyball involves a number of strict rules, including:

Players are allowed to touch the ball three times maximum before they return it across the court – blocks included.
There are a number of moves and hits that are classed as illegal in Beach Volleyball, including “hand touches”, “tips” and “dinks”.
Players are permitted to cross below the net in Beach Volleyball – but this will be classed as a foul if it tampers or interferes with the opposing teams play.
There is no set position for players, meaning they can move to any part of the court they wish at any time – provided it is on their side.
</string>

    <string name="s6_rules">
Rules of Boxing
In professional boxing, bouts take place over 12 three minute rounds with one minute rest between rounds.
The only method of attack is punching with a clenched fist and you may not strike below the belt, in the kidneys or the back of your opponents head or neck.
You cannot use the ropes for leverage.
You cannot hit an opponent when they are down.
A boxer hit with a low blow can take five minutes to recover.
If an unintentional foul (such as a clash of heads) ends the fight before four rounds are completed this is a “no contest”, from the fifth onwards the decision goes to the judge’s cards and is either a technical decision for either fighter or a technical draw.
</string>

    <string name="s7_rules">
Rules of Canoe Slalom
Tiebreaks
Athletes take two runs at the course during the heats. If any athletes are tied after both runs, they will all progress to the semifinals. If any athletes are tied in the semifinals, again, they will all move on to the final. If there are ties during the final, the gold medal will be shared by all the boats that tied for first place.

Penalties
Athletes can incur time penalties by failing to adhere to rules and regulations whilst competing on the course, and a certain number of seconds will be added to their finishing time as punishment. Penalties can be given for:

Touching a gate pole with a paddle or the boat itself (2 second penalty)
Taking a gate incorrectly – which includes missing the gate, displacing it by more than 45 degrees, or going through the gate upsidedown (50 second penalty)
Boat Dimensions
All canoe and kayak boats are required to meet certain criteria in terms of their size, shape, weight and length. The measurement rules are as follows:

K1 Boats: 3.50m minimum length, 0.6m minimum width, 8kg minimum weight
C1 Boats: 3.50m minimum length, 0.6m minimum width, 8kg minimum weight
C2 Boats: 4.10m minimum length, 0.75 minimum width, 13kg minimum weight
</string>

    <string name="s8_rules">
    Rules of Canoe Sprint
    Canoe Sprint races take place over 200 metres, 500 metres and 1000 metres.
    Lanes are assigned depending on performances in the heats. The winners are awarded the centre lanes, which are deemed to be slightly advantageous.
    In team events, no members of the crew can be swapped at any time, regardless of injury, illness or any other mitigating factors. Any team or athlete who cannot perform for any reason will be disqualified.
    Committing any of the following fouls may result in a warning or complete disqualification:
    Arriving late for the race
    Missing a race
    Committing two false starts
    Breaking the 5metre rule, which dictates that boats must remain inside a 5 metre boundary in their lane at all times
    All boats will also be subject to checks at the end of the race to ensure they have complied with preagreed rules and regulations. Any boat found to have failed to adhere to these rules (such as weighing in light) would be disqualified.
    An athlete or team is permitted to protest a caution or warning, but must do so immediately after the end of the race (20minutes maximum) to the competition committee. The committee will make a prompt decision, and if the athlete/team does not agree with this ruling, they are allowed to then approach the jury within the next 20minutes. Any ruling made by the jury is final.
    </string>

    <string name="s9_rules">
SOME BASIC RULES FROM THE BMX RULE BOOK
Children under 8 years of age are called “Sprocket Rockets” and their class is noncompetitive. No race points are awarded, and every rider gets a participation trophy at the end of the season.
At the start gate your front wheel must be in contact with the gate throughout the start call sequence.
Each rider must stay in their lane for at least the first 10 metres of the race track.
Riders must always travel in the correct race direction around the race track.
All competitors leading you by more than a wheel length have right of way over you and you may not deliberately hinder them.
If you are forced off the track during a race you may reenter the race track at the nearest point possible, provided this does not deliberately shorten your race distance. You must also give way to riders already on the track.
Competitors may not use team tactics in a race. All racers must run their own race.
A rider may not deliberately force another rider off the track.
For your finishing position to count you must cross the finish line with your bike (if it is unrideable due to a crash or malfunction, it is permissible to push, drag or carry it with you over the line).
Bad language and/or inappropriate behaviour by competitors or their supporters is not permitted at BMX events. Sanctions can be applied to riders for offences against this rule. BMX is an equal opportunity sport, so bias based on gender, race, religion, etc is also not permissible.
Drug use is forbidden.
BMX is an alcohol and smoke free sport.
</string>

    <string name="s11_rules">
Rules for cycling mountain bike

1) Trails are open for hiking, running, and biking. Please remember that some trails are only accessible for hiking. Look for signs like the one shown right to determine whether or not a trail is accessible.

2) Bikers must wear helmets and eye protection.

3) Ride only on approved trails.

4) Always yield.  Pass with care and keep your speed to a slow safe pace.  Approach each bend as if someone were around the corner.  Pay extra attention when crossing the Longleaf Trace.

5) Leave no trace.  Do not ride when ground is soft.  Never ride off trail.  Never skid your tires.  Never discard any object.

6) Trails are only open during daylight hours.

7) No motorized vehicles allowed.

8) All pets must be leashed.

9) No alcoholic beverages or illegal drugs allowed on the property.

Special rules for bicycle riders
You may perform hook turns at intersections unless prohibited by sign posting.
You do not need to give a left or stop signal, or signal when making a hook turn.
You may ride two abreast but not more than 1.5 metres apart.
You may overtake two other bicycle riders who are riding sidebyside.
You may travel in a Bus Lane, Tram Lane, Transit Lane or Truck Lane but not in a Bus Only Lane.
You may ride to the left of a continuous white edge line.
You may overtake on the left of stopped and slow moving vehicles.
</string>

    <string name="s10_rules">
Track Cycling Rules And Regulations
The track must be from 250 to 333.33 meters in length. To convert the Velodrome into the fastest track, it angles 42 degrees at its steepest point.
Even the internal conditions are also customized such as maintaining high temperature and air still in hopes to break the previous Olympic records! With such cuttingedge stateofart, riders are expected to cross the speed of 75mph.
According to the UCI rules, the flying 200 m time trial is the first round of competition for the athletes to qualify for the sprint competition. In this round, every rider finishes 2 to 3 warm up laps and then finishes the final 200 m, which is generally just under a lap.
If you envy the physique of Chris Hoy, then start working out religiously! Yes, a lot of exercise is required to build up strong and tough thighs similar to Chris Hoy’s with a circumference of 27in  enabling him to get from zero to 44mph in less than 10 seconds! Thus, athletes are supposed to work out well to build up their stamina and to eliminate body fat.
</string>

    <string name="s12_rules">
Track Cycling Rules And Regulations
The track must be from 250 to 333.33 meters in length. To convert the Velodrome into the fastest track, it angles 42 degrees at its steepest point.
Even the internal conditions are also customized such as maintaining high temperature and air still in hopes to break the previous Olympic records! With such cuttingedge stateofart, riders are expected to cross the speed of 75mph.
According to the UCI rules, the flying 200 m time trial is the first round of competition for the athletes to qualify for the sprint competition. In this round, every rider finishes 2 to 3 warm up laps and then finishes the final 200 m, which is generally just under a lap.
If you envy the physique of Chris Hoy, then start working out religiously! Yes, a lot of exercise is required to build up strong and tough thighs similar to Chris Hoy’s with a circumference of 27in  enabling him to get from zero to 44mph in less than 10 seconds! Thus, athletes are supposed to work out well to build up their stamina and to eliminate body fat.
</string>

    <string name="s13_rules">
Rules of Diving
The rule of diving a relatively straightforward, but differ slightly between the two main disciplines, springboard diving and platform diving.
</string>

    <string name="s14_rules">
rules for equestrian dressage
A ground jury consisting of various judges and officials and qualified according to FEI standards inspects the course and judges the competition.
Horses must be at least 9 years old for Olympic competition.
 A bell is used to communicate with the competitor and is used to signal various events such as when they may enter the arena, a halt or continue in case of an interruption or to indicate the rider is eliminated.
Red or white flags are used to mark obstacles or mandatory turns.
 Jumps generally are categorized as spreads, verticals or water jumps. Jumps may be set up in combinations.
Faults and Penalties

    Four faults are given for each jump knocked down. (A rail, or one or more parts of the jump fall to the ground).
    Four faults are given if one or more hooves leave an impression on the lath surrounding a water jump.
    Four faults are given for the first disobedience (refusal to jump, run out).
</string>

    <string name="s15_rules">
rules for equestrian eventing

The day ticket restricts you to 4 events per year, as only 4 day tickets can be purchased per rider, per year.
Riders under the age of 16 can only compete in Intro, PN, JRN and classes confined to Juniors following accreditation and registration with a Junior Regional Novice Coordinator.
Horses must be over 148cm (14.2hh) to compete in a british eventing competition, but horses between 142 and 148cm (14.0 and 14.2hh) can also compete on a day ticket, but only up to (and including) PreNovice events.
Horses may not compete until the calendar year in which they turn five.
</string>

    <string name="s16_rules">
rules for equestrian jumping

The day ticket restricts you to 4 events per year, as only 4 day tickets can be purchased per rider, per year.
Riders under the age of 16 can only compete in Intro, PN, JRN and classes confined to Juniors following accreditation and registration with a Junior Regional Novice Coordinator.
Horses must be over 148cm (14.2hh) to compete in a british eventing competition, but horses between 142 and 148cm (14.0 and 14.2hh) can also compete on a day ticket, but only up to (and including) PreNovice events.
Horses may not compete until the calendar year in which they turn five.
</string>

    <string name="s17_rules">
Rules of Fencing
Fencers must salute one another and the referee at the beginning and end of the bout, with failure to do so can result in the loss of a point (the winner) or even suspension (the loser).
Points are scored by hitting your opponent in accordance with the specific requirements for the type of weapon being used (as detailed above).
In foil, strikes outside the target area stop the contest before resuming afresh, however strikes with the blade (whilst not counting) do not stop the action; the latter rule also applies to the epée.
Barging the opponent, using your hand to cover the target zone or foot faults can lead to a points penalty at the referee’s discretion.
</string>

    <string name="s18_rules">
Rules of Football (Soccer)
A match consists of two 45 minutes halves with a 15 minute rest period in between.
Each team can have a minimum off 11 players (including 1 goalkeeper who is the only player allowed to handle the ball within the 18 yard box) and a minimum of 7 players are needed to constitute a match.
The field must be made of either artificial or natural grass. The size of pitches is allowed to vary but must be within 100130 yards long and 50100 yards wide. The pitch must also be marked with a rectangular shape around the outside showing out of bounds, two six yard boxes, two 18 yard boxes and a centre circle. A spot for a penalty placed 12 yards out of both goals and centre circle must also be visible.
The ball must have a circumference of 5861cm and be of a circular shape.
Each team can name up to 7 substitute players. Substitutions can be made at any time of the match with each team being able to make a maximum of 3 substitutions per side. In the event of all three substitutes being made and a player having to leave the field for injury the team will be forced to play without a replacement for that player.
Each game must include one referee and two assistant referee’s (linesmen). It’s the job of the referee to act as time keeper and make any decisions which may need to be made such as fouls, free kicks, throw ins, penalties and added on time at the end of each half. The referee may consult the assistant referees at any time in the match regarding a decision. It’s the assistant referee’s job to spot offside’s in the match (see below), throw ins for either team and also assist the referee in all decision making processes where appropriate.
If the game needs to head to extra time as a result of both teams being level in a match then 30 minutes will be added in the form of two 15 minute halves after the allotted 90 minutes.
If teams are still level after extra time then a penalty shootout must take place.
The whole ball must cross the goal line for it to constitute as a goal.
For fouls committed a player could receive either a yellow or red card depending on the severity of the foul; this comes down to the referee’s discretion. The yellow is a warning and a red card is a dismissal of that player. Two yellow cards will equal one red. Once a player is sent off then they cannot be replaced.
If a ball goes out of play off an opponent in either of the side lines then it is given as a throw in. If it goes out of play off an attacking player on the base line then it is a goal kick. If it comes off a defending player it is a corner kick.
</string>

    <string name="s19_rules">
Rules of Golf
The ball must be hit using standard clubs from the start of each hole to the green and ultimately into the hole, which is marked by a flag.
Players strike the ball in turn with the furthest away from the hole going first. At the start of a new hole whoever took the least shots on the preceding hole shall go first.
The penalty for a lost ball is one stroke and this includes balls struck out of bounds (off that particular hole) or into water hazards. You have five minutes to search for your ball and the penalty is both stroke (one shot) if the ball is lost and additionally distance (you play again from your original starting point) if it goes out of bounds or into the water.
Players can only use up to 14 clubs.
Players cannot seek advice from anyone other than their partner or caddy.
The ball should be played as it is found – you must not move, break or bend anything fixed or growing, other than to assume your normal stance, to improve the lie of the ball, your line of site or your area of swing.
On the putting green a player can mark, lift and clean his ball so long as it is replaced exactly where it was. He or she may also repair ball marks or hole plugs but not spike marks that are on the putting line.
</string>

    <string name="s20_rules">
Artistic Gymnastics Rules and Regulations
 There are six apparatus for men and four for women.

 Men and women compete in floor and vault events.

 Men only compete in the bars, rings and horse events while women only compete in uneven bars and the balance beam.

 Scoring is determined by a panel of nine referees.

Pommel Horse: a 1.15m tall apparatus with two handles on top.

Rings: two parallel rings are suspended 2.75m off the ground and 50cm apart.

Vault: Gymnasts sprint 25m towards a solid apparatus and jump onto its 120cm x 95cm surface.

Floor: square mat measuring at 12m x 12m with a 1m safety border provide added boost for gymnasts.

Horizontal Bars: gymnasts use a steel bar 2.65m off the ground.

Uneven Bars: upper bar is 2.4m off the floor and the lower bar is 1.6m.

Parallel Bars: supported by two wooden rails and is adjustable in height.

Balance Beam: gymnasts perform on a bar 5m long and 10cm wide.

Arabesque: balanced position typical in beam and floor exercises where the gymnast keeps one foot on the beam and raises the other behind them with arms extended.

Handstand: One of the most basic pses in artistic gymnastics, involving balancing the upright body with both hands on the beam.

Twisting Somersault: A somersault during which the gymnast rotates around the axis of the body a full 360 degrees.
</string>

    <string name="s21_rules">
Rhythmic Gymnastics Rules And Regulations
The Olympic athletes should be at least 16 years old at the end of Olympic Year
There are two events in the Olympic Competition Individual AllAround in which the athlete performs on the floor with a hoop, ball, clubs, or ribbon. The second event is the Group AllAround in which a total of 5 gymnasts compete in two sets of rounds
The standard measurement of the floor area is 13m by 13m
The permitted time for any individual exercise is between 1 minute 15 seconds and 1 minute 30 seconds and 2 minute 15 seconds to 2 minutes 30 seconds for group exercise
The highest score is fixed at 20.0 for each of the events and it is judged on the execution of the stunt and choreography
The Execution Score or E is scored out of 10.0 and points are deducted for technical faults like incorrect catch of the apparatus or losing the apparatus
The Artistic Score or A has a maximum of 10.0 and is marked for the music and choreography
The Difficulty Score or D begins at 0 and is scored to a maximum of 10.0 points
For the Final Composition Scoring, Artistic Score and Difficulty Score is added and an average is taken. (A+D divided by 2)
</string>

    <string name="s22_rules">
Rules of Handball
A match consists of two periods of 30 minutes each.
Each team consists of 7 players; a goalkeeper and 6 outfield players.
Outfield players can touch the ball with any part of their body that is above the knee.
Once a player receives possession, they can pass, hold possession or shoot.
If a player holds possession, they can dribble or take three steps for up to three seconds without dribbling.
Only the goalkeeper is allowed to come into contact with the floor of the goal area.
Goalkeepers are allowed out of the goal area but must not retain possession if they are outside the goal area.
</string>

    <string name="s23_rules">
HOCKEYS THREE MAIN RULES
Offsides: When any member of the attacking team precedes the puck over the defending teams blue line.

Offside (or twoline)Pass: When a player passes the puck from his defending zone to a teammate beyond the red center line.

Icing: When a player shoots the puck across the center red line and past the opposing red goal line. Icing is not called if the players team is killing a penalty, a teammate of the player shooting the puck touches it before a player from the opposing team, the defending goalie touches the puck first or if the puck travels through the crease (semicircle of blue paint at the "mouth" of the goal) on its way to the red line.
</string>

    <string name="s24_rules">
Rules of Judo
Judo matches take place on tatami (mats) measuring 14m x 14m, with a combat area of 10m x 10m marked out within it. Judokas (athletes) must bow before stepping onto the mat and must bow to each other before and after either practice or competition.
Judokas must wear the appropriate gi (uniforms), that is one that is no more than 5cm above the ankles and wrists and is tied with the correct style of knotted belt.
Bouts last five minutes (in international competition) and are won when one judoka is awarded ippon. If no ippon is awarded, the player with the highest score at the end of the bout is declared the winner. If the score are level the match is decided by a period of Golden Score then – if still not resolved – the decision of the referee and corner judges.
Penalties are awarded for minor (shido) or major (hansoku make) infringements of the rules. Four shidos results in the award of ippon to the opponent, as does one hansoku make.
Judokas must not employ any of the outlawed techniques, including attacking joints (other than the elbow), punching or kicking opponents, touching the opponent’s face, or intentionally injuring the opponent in any way.
</string>

    <string name="s25_rules">
Rules of Marathon Swimming  Marathon Swimmers Federation

This document was written by four wellestablished marathon swimmers, three of whom are USMS members. MSF Rules are intended as guidance for swimmers wishing to attempt a standard, traditional marathon swim in bodies of water where there is no local governing body.

They are also intended as a clear statement about the "spirit" of the sport which underlies these rules, so any popular media who report on marathon swimming in the future will not be confused or misled on this issue.

MSF Rules have been endorsed by an impressive (and growing) list of marathon swimmers and aspiring marathon swimmers. For further info, please see the ongoing discussion at the Marathon Swimmers Forum, and the coverage by Swimming World and SwimSwam.
</string>

    <string name="s26_rules">
Rules of Modern Pentathlon
All five sports involved in Modern Pentathlon have different rules and regulations that athletes must follow.

Fencing Rules
In Modern Pentathlon fencing, athletes must use an Epee that has a curve of less than 1 cm, and must not strike an opponent before the command “Allez!” is shouted or after the command “Halte!” is announced. Doing so will lead to penalisation.

Swimming Rules
During the swimming stage, athletes are permitted to swim underwater for the first 15 metres, but after this point must keep some of their body above the surface. Athletes must touch the wall when they reach the end of the pool and turn back, and cannot obstruct an opponent in any way during a race.

Show Jumping Rules
Athletes must show respect, courtesy and professionalism during the show jumping stage of the Modern Pentathlon. The horse must follow directions, timing, and stay within the competition court, and if there is any evidence of poor treatment toward the animal, the athlete is promptly disqualified.

Shooting and Cross Country Racing Rules
During the combination event at the end of the Modern Pentathlon, athletes must wait until the minimum shooting time is over at the pistol stage before they can begin running again. Athletes found to be obstructing opponents in any way will risk being disqualified from the entire event.
</string>

    <string name="s27_rules">
Rules of Rowing
Competitive rowing involves a number of rules that athletes must adhere to in order to avoid being disqualified. These include:

Lane Changing: There are six separate lanes in an Olympic rowing event, with one lane assigned to each boat. Athletes and teams are actually allowed to move across from one lane to another if they desire – provided they do not impede or obstruct another boat whilst doing so.
False Starts: Boats must not leave the starting line until the firing gun goes off. Athletes/teams are allowed one “false” start (i.e. setting off before they are permitted to do so). If they do this twice, however, they will be disqualified from the race.
Olympic Medal Winners: The gold, silver and bronze Olympic games medals are awarded to the boats that finish in the top three of the final race, which has six teams/athletes competing.
</string>

    <string name="s28_rules">
Rules of Rugby
The game is broken down into two 40 minute halves with a 10 minute rest period in between. The game carries no stoppage time and will end exactly on 80 minutes.
Each team can start with 15 players and up to 7 substitutes. Players that have left the field are only allowed to return if they have been treated for an injury.
The field must be roughly 100 metres long and 70 metres wide with a minimum of a 10 metre dead ball area. The H shaped goal needs to be 6 metres wide with no restrictions on height.
The field consist of the following markings; half way line, 5 metre line, 22 metre line, 10 metre line and dead ball line. Also included is a centre spot for restarting the game after a try, penalty or drop goal has been scored.
The game must have one referee and two touch judges. It’s the referee’s job to time keep, make decisions throughout the game and keep order on the field. The two touch judges can assist the referee with decisions and also notify the referee when players are in touch (out of playing boundaries).
The game will stop if a player is fouled, the ball goes out of play or a try or drop goal is scored.
The defending team must tackle a player by grabbing a hold and pulling them to the floor. A tackle cannot be made above shoulder height and doing so will cause the referee to award a foul.
Once the ball goes into touch a line out is called. Up to 7 players can enter a line out and any of these players can be lifted in order to catch the ball being thrown in. Both teams can compete to win the ball.
A successful conversion, penalty or kick at goal only occurs when the player manages to kick the ball through the top section of the goal. If a player is unsuccessful the ball is still in play until it crosses one of the playing fields boundaries.
Attacking players must remain behind the ball whilst active or run the risk of being called offside. Players not interfering with play can be in front of ball but must get back behind the ball before then again interfering with play.
</string>

    <string name="s29_rules">
Sailing Rules And Regulations
Olympic sailing discipline has certain rules and regulations that need to be strictly followed by the sailors. These rules are:
The most important rule in the discipline of sailing is the rule of ‘Right of Way’. There are three basic right of way rules:
The boat on starboard path has the right of way, when the boats on opposite tacks meet.
In a situation where boats on the same path are next to each other, the boat which is nearest to the wind must stay clear.
When two boats are in the same direction but are not besides each other, the overtaking boat must stay clear.
If a boat contravenes the ‘right of way’ rules, it may be penalized instantly. This means the boat will be turned in two full circles (also known as 720). This penalty can be enforced on any boat except 49ers and Tornadoes which have to complete only one circle (a 360). If a sailor is not ready to accept this punishment, he/she may be disqualified. These significant ‘right of way’ rules are relevant both during the competition and before the race begin when the boats are in the attempt to place themselves for a speedy start.
If a sailor crosses the line ahead of time, he/she should round the beginning buoy and resume the race. Otherwise, the athlete may be disqualified. If a race committee is unable to judge which boats have crossed the line before time, a general recall is sounded.
If a sailor has a strong opinion that another one has broken the rules and regulations of the sport, he/she can object. To do so, the protester must shout "protest" at the supposed offender and hoist a red protest flag. At the end of the race, the protester has 90 minutes time to lodge the complaint, which is the looked upon by an independent panel of five International Sailing Federation jurors.
During the competition, there is onwater umpiring, which comprises of the umpire boats trailing the competitors and penalizing them on the spot if such a situation arises.
Only the Mistral sailboard is permitted to touch a buoy. The penalty for other boats is 360, except in cases where the sailor is able to persuade the jury that the boat was enforced into the buoy by another boat.
It is mandatory for the sailors to wear buoyancy aids and there are certain weight limits set with respect to the outfits and equipment worn by the athletes.
There specific time frame within which the races must be concluded. For instance, an hour for 49ers and Mistrals, 1.5 hours for Europes, Lasers, Tornadoes and 470s and two hours for Stars, Solings and Finns. While planning out the courses for the races, the race committee takes these time limits into consideration.
The authority can modify or condense the courses or discard the race altogether, after taking onwater conditions into consideration. The athletes will be informed about these changes by flowing a system of flags from the committee boat.
</string>


    <string name="s30_rules">
shooting
The shooting competition is split into three separate disciplines; rifle, pistol and shotgun, with each event defined by the weapon used by the competitors. Athletes then compete over a variety of distances, either 10 meters, 25 meters or 50 meters, and in a selection of poses either standing, kneeling or prone; which sees them lie on their front.

Each shooter will enter a qualifying round which ranges between 20 and 120 shots, with the top eight progressing to the final. Shots are taken within a particular time frame. In the medal final, shooters are eliminated over a 20shot competition based on their success, until just two competitors remain to battle for gold. Count back is used as a tiebreaker if shooters are level.
</string>

    <string name="s31_rules">
swimming
By definition, a freestyle swimmer can use any stroke. But the fastest is the "Australian crawl" (also known as the "front crawl"), which is characterized by an alternating overhand motion of the arms and a flutter or scissor kick. The arm movement has three distinct segments: pull, push and recovery. A twobeatper stroke kick is used in distance races; a faster, sixbeat kick is used in sprint events and in the final stretch of distance races. Breathing patterns vary depending on the distance of an event and a competitors preferred style; in the 50m freestyle, for example, some competitors dont breathe at any point in the race.

Freestyle has been swum at every modern Olympics. Today, distances contested are 50m, 100m, 200m, 400m, 800m (women only), 1500m (men only) and 10k open water. There also are two freestyle relay races: 4x100m and 4x200m.
</string>

    <string name="s32_rules">
synchronized swimming
Before participating in the Olympics, the swimmers must clear the qualifying competitions

If we focus on Olympics, there are only two events played in each Olympics i.e. team and duet

There are two routines included here one is free routine and one is technical routine

Players can perform both in team and duets

Technical routine is predetermined and should be performed strictly according to certain elements

Free routine is not predetermined so the players are free to do their performance and in free routine, they have to show their creativity in choreography, dancing, and coordination

In duet event, there are two swimmers and one alternate swimmer. In free routine, the time limit is 3:30 minutes and in technical routine time limit is 2:20 minutes

In team event, there are eight swimmers and one alternate swimmer. Time limit in free routine is 4:00 minutes and 2:50 minutes in technical routine

In each event, there is relaxation of utmost 15 seconds

The judges give points according to the level of difficulty of the performance shown by the players

Marks awarded ranges from 0.0 to 10.0
</string>

    <string name="s33_rules">
Table Tennis
 The table shall be in surface rectangular, 274 cm. (9 ft.) in length, 152.5 cm. (5 ft.) in width. It shall be supported so that its upper surface, termed the playing surface, shall lie in a horizontal plane 76 cm. (2 ft. 6 in.) above the floor.
1.2 It shall be made of any material and shall yield a uniform bounce of about 23 cm. (8 3/4 in.) when a standard ball is dropped from a height of 30 cm. (12 in.) above the surface.
1.3 The playing surface shall be dark colored and matt, with a white line 2 cm. (3/4 inch) wide along each edge.
1.3.1 The lines along the 152.5 cm. (5 ft.) edges or ends shall be termed end lines, and they shall be regarded as extending indefinitely in both directions.
1.3.2 The lines along the 274 cm. (9 ft.) edges or sides shall be termed side lines.
1.4 For doubles, the playing surface shall be divided into halves by a white line 3 mm. (1/8 in.) wide, running parallel with the side lines, termed the center line. Permanent marking of the center line shall not invalidate the table for singles play. The center line shall be regarded as part of each right hand court.
1.5 The playing surface shall be considered to include the top edges of the table, but not the sides of the table top below the edge.
</string>


    <string name="s34_rules">
rules for taekwondo
Taekwondo matches should be contested by competitors of the same sex and in the same classified weight category.
The competition area is a mat that measures 8 metres squared.
Taekwondo matches are contested over 3 x 2 minute rounds with a rest of 1 minute between rounds.
Each fighter attempts to knockout their opponent or score points by landing blows on their opponent’s torso or head. Kicks are allowed to both to the torso and head, whilst punches are only allowed to the body. Below the waist is not a permitted target.
If a fighter and their coach think that a point has been missed or that a mistake has been made, they can make a protest. A video replay is then looked at by judges and a decision is made.
Fighters can lose points by the way of penalties. These can be incurred by actions such as:
Punching to the face
Attacking with the knee
Attacking below the waist
Stepping out of the ring with both feet
Turning your back on your opponent
Pushing, holding or grabbing your opponent
Feigning injury
The match is won by the fighter who knocks their opponent out or who has the greater number of points at the end of the three rounds.
If the match is a draw, a golden point round is fought, with the fighter landing the first scoring point being declared the winner.
</string>

    <string name="s35_rules">
rules for tennis
The game starts with a coin toss to determine which player must serve first and which side they want to serve from.
The server must then serve each point from alternative sides on the base line. At no point must the server’s feet move in front of the baseline on the court prior to hitting their serve.
If the server fails to get their first serve in they may take advantage of a second serve. If they again fail to get their second serve in then a double fault will be called and the point lost.
If the server clips the net but the ball goes in the service area still then let is called and they get to take that serve again without penalty. If the ball hits the net and fails to go in the service area then out is called and they lose that serve.
The receiver may stand where they wish upon receipt of the serve. If the ball is struck without the serve bouncing then the server will receive the point.
Once a serve has been made the amount of shots between the players can be unlimited. The point is won by hitting the ball so the opponent fails to return it in the scoring areas.
Points are awarded in scores of 15, 30 and 40. 15 represent 1 point, 30 = 2 and 40 = 3. You
need 4 points to win a game. If a game lands on 4040 it’s known as deuce. From deuce a player needs to win 2 consecutive points to win the game. After winning one point from deuce they player is on advantage. If the player wins the next point they win the game, if they lose it goes back to deuce.
To win the set a player must win 6 games by 2 or more. The opening sets will go to a tie break if its ends up 66 where players play first to 7 points. The final set will not have a tie break and requires players to win by two games with no limits.
If a player touches the net, distracts his opponent or impedes in anyway then they automatically lose the point.
The ball can hit any part of the line for the point to be called in, outside the line and the ball is out.
The balls in a tennis match are changed for new balls every 6 games
A player loses a point if they fail to return the ball in either the correct areas on the court, hits the net and doesn’t go into opponent’s area or fails to return the ball before it bounces twice in their half.
</string>

    <string name="s36_rules">
rules for trampoline
The trampoline shall not be used without adult supervision.
The trampoline may not be moved to another location.
All toys, bikes, and people must remain at least 2.5 meters (about8 feet) from the trampoline when it is in use.
Only one person may use the trampoline at a time.
Always jump in the middle of the trampoline.
No somersaults or flips.
Do not jump exit the trampoline; always climb down.
If the trampoline is wet, it may not be used.
The safety net and padding may not be removed at any time.
All jewelry and hair clips must be removed prior to using the trampoline
</string>

    <string name="s37_rules">
rules for triathlon
Other rules of triathlon vary from race to race and generally involve descriptions of allowable equipment (for example, wetsuits are allowed in USAT events in the swimming stage of some races when the water temperature is below 78.1 °F [25.6 °C]),[30] and prohibitions against interference between athletes.[34] Additionally, the use of flippers or other swim propulsion and flotation aids are illegal in triathlon and can result in disqualification.[30]

One rule involving the cycle leg is that the competitors helmet must be donned before the competitor mounts (or even takes possession of, in certain jurisdictions[35]) the bike and must remain on until the competitor has dismounted; the competitor is not required to wear the helmet when not on the bicycle (e.g. while repairing a mechanical problem). Failure to comply with this rule will result in disqualification.[30][34] Additionally, while on the bike course, all bicycles shall be propelled only by human force and human power. Other than pushing a bicycle, any propulsive action brought on by use of the hands is prohibited. Should a competitors bike malfunction they can proceed with the race as long as they are doing so with their bicycle in tow.[30] There are also strict rules regarding the bike mount line. Competitors may not begin riding their bicycle out of transition until they are over a clearly marked line. Mounting the bike prior to this may incur a penalty (example: a 15second time penalty at the London 2012 Olympics was awarded to Jonathan Brownlee, a competitor from Great Britain, for mounting his bike too early.)[34][36]

Other time penalties can be incurred during the race for, among other things, drafting on the bike in a nondrafting race, improper passing, littering on course, and unsportsmanlike conduct.[30][37]

Triathlon and fitness

Triathletes competing in the swim component of race. Wetsuits are common but not universal
Participants in triathlon often use the sport to improve or maintain their physical fitness.[38][39] With each sport being an endurance event, training for a triathlon provides cardiovascular exercise benefits.[40] Additionally, triathletes encounter fewer injuries than those who only use running as part of their exercise routine due to the incorporation of low impact swim and bike training.[41]

Triathletes spend many hours training for competitions, like other endurance event participants.[42] There are three components that have been researched to improve endurance sports performance; aerobic capacity, lactate threshold, and economy.[43] Injuries that are incurred from long hours of a single activity are not as common in triathlon as they are in single sport events. The crosstraining effect that athletes achieve from training for one sport by doing a second activity applies to triathlon training.[41] Additional activities that triathletes perform for crosstraining benefits are yoga, pilates, and weight training.
</string>

    <string name="s38_rules">
Rules of Volleyball
Each team consist of 6 players and 6 substitutes. Players can be substituted at any time but if they are to return can only be swapped for the player that replaced them.
Each team can hit the ball up to three times before the ball must be returned. The defensive team can then try and block or return the ball again hitting it a maximum of three times.
Games are played up to 25 points and must be won by 2 clear points.
Violations will be called for the following:
Stepping over the base line when serving the ball.
Ball hits the net and fails to get over the net (If the ball hits the net and still goes over the net then this is perfectly legal).
Players are not allowed to carry, palm or run with the ball.
Players must not touch the net with any part of the body. If the net is said to have hit them rather than viceversa, then this is ok.
The ball cannot travel under the net.
Players cannot reach over the net and hit the ball.
</string>

    <string name="s39_rules">
Rules of Water Polo
The playing area is 30m x 20m with a minimum depth of 2m.
Teams consist of 13 players in total, with 7 players in play at any time, 6 field players and 1 goalie.
Players are only permitted to use one hand to hold the ball apart from the goalie who can use two hands when within 5m of their own goal.
Water Polo is played in four quarters with each quarter lasting for eight minutes with a two minute break between quarters.
Players advance the ball upfield by swimming with the ball in front of them or by passing to teammates.
Players are not allowed to touch the bottom of the pool and players tread water or swim for the entire match.
Teams can only retain the ball for up to 30 seconds without shooting at goal.
A goal is equal to one point and is scored when the ball is pushed or thrown completely between the goalposts and under the crossbar.
Fouls are made up of ordinary fouls and major fouls. Players are only allowed three major fouls, any more and they are excluded out of the game.
If at the end of the game the score remains tied, a shootout occurs to decide the winner.
</string>

    <string name="s40_rules">
Weightlifting Rules and Regulations
 There are two weightlifting techniques, the "snatch" and the clean and jerk".

 Snatch entails lifting the bar from the floor above the head in one movement.

 Clean and jerk is a twostage movement, lifting the bar from the ground to shoulder height, and then again over the head.

 Athletes are allowed three attempts with a final score combining the totals.

 Depending on successful attempts, the weight is increased by at least 1kg.

 For men, the bar is 2.2m long and weighs 20kg. For women, the bar is 2.01m long and weighs 15kg.

Collars: metal components used for fixing the weights on the bar.

Weighin: procedure conducted two hours prior to the event to ensure all athletes are within the correct body weight.

Pressout: illegal movement where the athlete does not fully extend the arms when the bar is raised.
</string>

    <string name="s41_rules">
rules for wrestling freestyle
Two3 minute periods with a 30 second break in between for Open, Junior, Cadet Divisions.
Two2 minute periods with a 30 second break in between for all Schoolboy/Schoolgirl and below divisions.
A Technical Fall is earned ONLY with a differential of 10 points between wrestlers and ends the match.
Slip throws are emphasized.  A slip throw is when an attacking wrestler who takes all of the risk does not complete the attack for a score and the defending wrestler does nothing aside from defending the attack of the other wrestler.  In this situation, no points are awarded and wrestlers are returned to the standing position.  Slip throws can occur from neutral as well as par terre (top and bottom) positions (in either case, wrestlers return to standing position).
Each wrestler receives a total of two minutes of injury time per match.
</string>

    <string name="s42_rules">
GrecoRoman Wrestling Rules and Regulations
 Wrestlers can only use their arms and upper body to defend or attack.

 A win by fall (pin) is achieved when both of the opponents shoulders are forced on to the mat at the same time.

 A win by technical fall is achieved when one wrestler gains an eightpoint advantage, at which point they are declared winner.

 Matches are contested over two periods of three minutes.

 Points are awarded for moves. Illegal moves include elbowing, striking with knees, strangulation, eyepokes and hairpulling.

 Referees control the action while judges keep score. The chairman oversees both referees and judges and declares technical superiority.

 Action takes place in the dark center circle, which is surrounded by an orange passivity area. Everything outside of that is out of bounds.

Challenge: each wrestler is allowed one video challenge per match.

Suplex: wrestler lifts his opponent high while falling backwards on his own neck in order to bring his opponents shoulders down.

Highamplitude Takedown: a highscoring throw in which the opponents feet go above his own head.
</string>




















    <!-- //******************************** END SPORTS INFO **************************************************************/  -->



</resources>